漫威影业
这片头音乐一听就来精神
That logo music just gets you pumped.
对吧
Right?
抱歉各位 我有点嗨过头了 咱们可是好久不见
I'm sorry. I just, I'm excited to be here. It's been a while.
被雪藏了这么长时间 我都不知道什么时候才有续集
You know, for a long time, I wasn't sure I'd ever be back.
迪士尼收购了福克斯
Disney bought Fox...
还有一堆无聊的版权手续 吧啦吧啦 快烦死了
there was a whole boring rights issue, blabbity-blabbity-blah.
但是呢 他们竟然点名要我
But then, it turned out, they wanted me.
漫威影业 荣誉出品
我原本不该有自己的独立电影
The one guywho shouldn't even have his own movie...
更别说一个系列了
much less a franchise.
凯文·费奇 制作的电影
漫威这蠢蛋
Marvel's so stupid.
看到这么个片名
Look, we know the title of this thing. So...
瑞安·雷诺兹全力数字公司 / 齐拉普斯娱乐 联合制作
我知道你们在想啥
I know what you're wondering.
剧情怎么编 才能不辱没罗根的一世英名
How are we gonna do this with out dishonoring Logan's memory?
我来告诉你们
And I'll tell you how.
其实我也不知道
We're not.
BGM：The Platters - 《Only You》 (Re-Recorded)
但是可以偷偷说一句
I'm gonna let you in on a little secret.
金刚狼没死
Wolverine is not dead.
《金刚狼3》导演与休·杰克曼在最开始都表示 其设定属于平行宇宙 所以影片中才会出现X战警的漫画
虽然作为一部悲剧电影 那个结局很完美
Sure, it made for a perfect ending to a very sad story.
【杯子】我喜欢我
但福克斯官方在上映后改口 设定为X战警主宇宙 可能是得到收购的消息 制造话题度
但是愈合因子的能力没那么简单
But that's not how regenerative healing factors work.
你以为我想来美丽的北达科他州
You think I wanna be out herein beautiful downtown North Dakota...
挖掘独一无二的金刚狼吗 才怪
digging up the one and only Wolverine? No, thank you.
但整个世界的命运危在旦夕
But the fate of my entire world is at stake.
他虽然未必活得滋润 但绝对还没...
He may not be living his best life, but he sure as hell ain't...
死透
dead.
挖到了
Bingo.
运气不错
Yahtzee.
对
Yes, yes, yes.
妈的
Damn it!
王八蛋
Son of a bitch!
你
You...
靠 操你妈
Christ. Motherfucker!
整个世界要操他妈的...
My world is fuck...
刚刚好奇怪
That was weird.
现在我冷静多了
I'm much calmer now.
虽然我不是科学家
Look, I'm not a man of science.
不过你应该是治不好了
But you seem incredibly passed away.
但还是很高兴见到你
But it's good to see ya.
老实说 我一直想跟你合作 罗根
I gotta be honest, I've always wanted to ride with you, Log.
咱们强强联合
You and me getting into it.
死侍与金刚狼大展身手
Deadpool and Wolverine just fucking shit up.
想想那有多好玩
Can you imagine the fun,
效果多炸裂
the chaos...
能分多少票房
the residuals?
"G'day, mate"是澳大利亚俚语 因休·杰克曼是澳大利亚人
"嗨 兄弟
"G'day, mate.
想让我活过来也不难 只要漫威拿钞票一砸 我立马满血复活"
"There's nothing that'll bring me back to life faster "than a big bag of Marvel cash."
我也这么觉得 休
Me too, Hugh.
你可别
But, no.
别 别 别
No, no, no.
你非得死得那么悲壮
You had to get all noble and die for real.
妈的
Goddamn it!
我现在真的需要你帮忙
I could really use your help right now.
等等
Wait!
警告你们 我不是一个人
I'm warning you, I'm not alone.
韦德·温斯顿·威尔逊
Wade Winston Wilson...
你已被时间管理局下令逮捕
you are under arrestby the Time Variance Authority...
已犯多项罪行
for too many crimes to list.
快出来
Come out...
-配合行动 我们将不会动用武力 -被群演追杀
-and we'll extend you the courtesy of taking you in one piece. -Death by day-player.
最后一次机会
Last chance.
放下武器 停止抵抗 出来跟我们走
Throw out your weaponsand come out peacefully.
我是不会放下武器的
I'm not gonna give you my weapons...
但我可以保证不用
but I promise not to use them.
人体有206根骨头
There are two hundred and six bones in the human body.
美剧《绯闻女孩》的主演之一 就是瑞安·雷诺兹的妻子布蕾克·莱弗利
看《绯闻女孩》时我会变成207根
Two hundred and seven if I'm watching Gossip Girl.
上吧 火力全开
Here we go. Maximum effort.
BGM：NSYNC - 《Bye Bye Bye》
小狼狗 最终我们也算组队了
Okay, peanut. Guess we're getting that team up after all.
肖恩·利维
执导的电影作品
领衔主演
瑞安·雷诺兹
饰 死侍 / 韦德·威尔逊
领衔主演
休·杰克曼
饰 金刚狼 / 罗根
主 演
艾玛·科林
饰 卡桑德拉·诺瓦
死侍"坟头蹦迪"特意选了金刚狼不喜欢的这首歌曲 详见《X战警2》43分52秒处
主 演
莫蕾娜·巴卡琳
饰 凡妮莎
主 演
罗伯·德兰尼
莱斯利·格塞斯
主 演
亚伦·斯坦福
马修·麦克费登
选角导演
萨拉·芬恩
音乐指挥
戴夫·乔丹
配 乐
罗伯·西蒙森
马拉多纳禁区外怒射
Maradona from outside the box!
球进了
Goal!
视觉特效制作
丽莎·马拉
视觉特效总监
斯温·吉尔伯格
服装设计
格雷厄姆·丘彻亚德
玛耶斯·C·鲁贝奥
改编 自
漫威漫画
电影剪辑 迪恩·齐默尔曼 / 沙恩·雷奥
艺术指导
雷蒙德·陈
摄影指导 乔治·瑞奇蒙
合伙制片
米切尔·贝尔
执行制片人
乔治.杜威
西蒙·金伯格
乔纳森·科马克·马丁
执行制片人
瑞特·里斯
保罗·韦尼克
执行制片人 温迪·雅各布森
玛丽·麦克拉格伦 / 乔什·麦克拉伦
执行制片人
路易斯·德·埃斯波西托
来啊 傻大个
Come on, big fella.
制片人
瑞安·雷诺兹
肖恩·利维
制片人
凯文·费奇
劳伦·舒勒·唐纳
编 剧
瑞安·雷诺兹 / 瑞特·里斯
保罗·韦尼克 / 扎布·威尔斯 / 肖恩·利维
导 演
肖恩·利维
我已经湿透了
I am soaking wet right now.
死 侍
与金刚狼
澄清一下 前面这一段我并不引以为傲
To be clear, I'm not proud of any of this.
血腥暴力 轻度恋尸 那不是我
The wanton violence, the whiff of necrophilia. It isn't who I am.
也不是我的人生目标
It isn't who I wanna be.
我想成为什么样的人呢
Who I wanna be?
为了帮你们搞懂
Well, to help you understand that...
我得带你回顾
I've gotta take you back.
我穿越时空的一段旅程...
A little joyride I took through space and time...
回到改变一切的那一天
to the day that changed everything.
【绿灯侠】
2018年3月14日
没想到我能坐在这里
I can't believe I'm finally here.
这一刻我盼了好久
I've waited for this moment for so long.
地球-616
先生 谢谢您抽空见我
Thank you, sir, for seeing me.
通常来讲 地球-616是漫画中的主宇宙 电影宇宙是地球-199999
神圣时间线
我深信...
I firmly believe...
由于一些人员变动 收购等客观原因 漫威主宇宙的相关信息中 这两个编号都出现过
我能够...
that my services could be of...
为贵司奉献绵薄之力 我知道...
great use to your organization. Now I know...
我曾因为在斯塔克大厦砸飞机被逮捕...
I was caught smashturbating in the lobby of Stark Tower...
-但我敢保证 -砸飞机？
-but I can assure you that... -Smashturbating?
抱歉 我没听明白
I'm sorry, what, what was that?
抱歉 就是拿出那些玩意...
No, I'm sorry. That, that's when you get those toy...
那应该是浩克的手
Hulk hands, right?
往下看着它 然后就是...
And then you just, you look down, and you just...
鼓起勇气 蹂躏你的命根子
you brace yourself, and you ravage the midsection.
-用力掐住...  -懂了 打住
-Pinch the... Yeah. Okay. -I get it. Okay, thank you.
-有画面了 -理解重点就好
-The picture's painted. -You get the gist.
你今天来到底是为了什么
What exactly brings you here today?
是这样 嗯
Why am I... Okay.
我一直在想
I care.
我知道我对待一切都言笑自若 但我想...
I know I turn everything into a joke, but I...
我想 我想把这种特长...
I care, and I, I wanna use that feeling...
用在更重要的地方
for something important.
我想有作为
I, I wanna matter.
让心爱的女人看到我有作为
I need to show my girl that I matter.
还有...
And...
我觉得说这些也是浪费感情
you know, I feel like I'm wasting the good stuff here.
-说了算的那位会来吗 -你是指谁
-Is the man not gonna be joining us? -The man?
我应该把这些话说给能做主的...
Yeah. I should save this if he's gonna...
你现在只要知道这里我说了算
As, as far as you're concerned right now, I'm the man.
-不是 -说了算的就是我
-No. -The man is me.
现在这一块归我管
I am the man in this circumstance.
他已经不管这些事了
He doesn't do this kind of thing anymore.
-客串？ -面试
-Cameos? -Meetings.
-面试 -初级面试
-Meetings. -Entry-level meetings.
初级？
Entry-level?
你不是当司机的吗
-Aren't you the chauffeur, maybe? -I...
大家经常误解
Common misconception.
我刚开始是斯塔克先生的司机
I did begin my career as Mr. Stark's driver.
-很快就转任... -专属司机 -安保主管
-Quickly pivoted to the Head of Security. -Chauffeur.
主管安保的... 明白
The Head of... Of course, yes, yes, yes.
所以我看了下你的履历
And why I am vetting your resume.
你似乎漏掉了 团队工作经验之类的表述
You seem to have left out whether or not you had any experience as a member of a team.
这方面能补充一下吗
Could you maybe add a little bit of perspective there?
没问题 我加入过特种部队...
No, yes, of course. I was Special Forces...
我还担任过X特攻队队长 也是创始人
but I was... Mainly, I was team leader founder, really, of X-Force.
可惜队员都在行动中阵亡了
Sadly, they, they all perished in action though.
当时是怎么回事
How exactly did that happen?
警方说死因是地球引力 但...
Well, the police say gravity, but if...
实际上...
Just between us...
-是因为他们人气不够高 -明白了
-they didn't test well in the focus group. -I see.
-尤其是电索 -X特攻队
-Particularly Cable. -X-Force.
我知道这次面试不顺利 请别记录下来 我...
Look, I can see this isn't going well. Please stop writing. Look, I, I...
我想...我想成为复仇者
I'm just... I wanna be an Avenger.
我想当复仇者
I wanna be an Avenger.
为什么想当复仇者
Why do you wanna be an Avenger?
你看看这里 他们是精英中的精英
Look around you. I mean, they're the, they're the best of the best.
做出了重大贡献
And, and what they do matters.
我需要成为复仇者
I need to be an Avenger.
女朋友正在跟我闹别扭 如果我...
Sir, my girl has kinda had it with my shtick, and I, if I don't, you know...
不能有所改变 善用我的天赋
turn things aroundand do something with my gifts...
恐怕就无法挽留她了 当然我也不怪她
I don't think it's gonna really work out for me and I wouldn't blame her.
复仇者联盟是一批很独特的超级英雄
Avengers are a very unique group of superheroes...
托尼·斯塔克有颗温暖的心
有独特的象征的意义 他们不仅仅是身披战衣去作战
that stand for something more than just fighting and wearing costumes.
漫威在2017年设定《钢铁侠2》中戴玩具头盔的男孩 是小时候的彼得·帕克
人们敬仰我们 孩子崇拜我们
I mean, people look up to us. Kids look up to us.
-人们... -你说"我们"？
-They... -I'm sorry. "Us?"
据说索尼不允许蜘蛛侠出现在本片中 所以用这个头盔挡住了照片中的彼得
从来没听说你也是复仇者
I wasn't aware that you were an Avenger.
准确的说 复仇者相关人员
Avengers-adjacent, technically.
你的超能力是什么 侧方停车？
What's your superpower? Is it parallel parking?
非常抱歉
I am so sorry.
话太损了
That was cruel.
我一紧张就爱嘴贱 下不为例
I lash out when I'm nervous. Won't happen again.
-我们直接说重点 -好的
-Let's cut to the chase. -Please.
你刚刚说的...
You just said moments ago...
你想当复仇者 是因为有需要
that you wanted to be an Avenger because you need it.
是的 没错
Yes, sir, I do.
他们之所以成为复仇者 不是自己需要
But the Avengers don't do the job because they need it.
而是民众需要他们
They do the job because people need them.
看到不同了吗
Do you see the distinction?
看到了
Yes, sir.
拜托 霍根先生
Please, Mr. Hogan.
我不想这一生 到死都碌碌无为
I don't wanna spend the rest of my life like an annoying one-trick pony.
先这样吧
All right.
老天 你站起来了
Oh, my God, you're standing.
今天的见面结束了
Yeah, now's the time that we stand.
完蛋了
Damn it.
问题可能在于...
Now, the problem might be that you're...
你有点好高骛远
reaching a little, little too high.
务实一点才不会失望
Aim for the middle, and you'll never miss.
你的出发点很好 我相信你
Right? I think you got a good heart. I believe what you're saying.
但并非人人都是当英雄的料 我就不是
But not everybody's the world-saving type. I'm not,
但我很快乐
and I'm happy.
因为我找到了自己的定位
Right? I found my place.
找出你的定位
Find your place.
继续努力
All right? Get back out there.
-我们会关注你的 加油 -好的
-We'll keep an eye on you. Good luck. -Okay.
我想让你开车带我去汉堡店
Fetch the car. I wanna hit Shake Shack.
面试失败还是挺饿的
Rejection makes me hungy.
这个确实...不行...
Really? No, no. Please.
-不行就算了 -谢谢
-Yeah, no, no, no.  -Okay, thank you.
俗话说得好
You know what they say.
上帝关上一扇门...
When one door closes...
地球-10005
会为你打开另一扇工作的门
your locker at work opens.
六 年 后
【韦德 业务顾问】
我们开始卖正规认证的二手车了 操你...
Now let's go sell some certified pre-owned vehicles, motherfu...
严格来说 嘉华不是小厢旅
Technically, the, the Carnival's not a minivan.
是多用途汽车
It's an MPV.
-如果跟本田奥德赛比起来怎么样 -奥德赛？
-So how does the Kia compare to the Honda Odyssey? -The Odyssey?
问得好 比那鸡巴车强多了
That's a great question. It doesn't fucking suck.
你可以不带脏话来回答的
You know, you can answer the question without swearing.
抱歉 我没...我还没孩子
I'm sorry, Tammy, I don't, I don't have kids.
不是我不想要孩子
Not that I haven't dreamt of that...
但我很久没中出过真鲍鱼了
but I don't have a lot of vaginal sex.
【DriveMax车行】
下次就会签单了
You'll get them next time, pal.
你随时都能做回超级英雄
And look, you can always go back to superhero-ing.
我希望你再穿上那套战衣
I mean, I know I'd like to see you back in the suit.
我放柜子里不是因为穿着方便
I don't keep it in my locker so that I can wear it.
而是以防有什么状况需要我们再次出动
I keep it in my locker in case we need to saddle up again.
放在这干嘛
What? What is that doing in there?
早结束了
I'm done.
结束了
心无牵挂 彻底放下了
And I'm fine with being done.
我理想是当销售？
Look, is sales the best match?
应该不是
Probably not.
这是我向往的生活状态吗 怎么可能
Is this the life that I always imagined for myself? Fuck no.
但这适合我 老伙计 真的
But this is the right fit for me, Sugar Bear, it is.
好吧 威尔逊先生
Okay, Mr. Wilson.
其实我们可以一个月接个小任务
I'm just saying, once a month, we could go on a little mission.
我们是人类 渴望有成就感
We're human beings. We crave purpose.
而且我们可是死侍
After all, we're Deadpool.
打住 我们不是死侍 我也早就不是了
Please stop saying that. We're not Deadpool. I'm not even Deadpool anymore.
如果你到中年危机了 就使劲折腾起来
Well, if you're gonna have a midlife crisis, go big.
几年前...
A few years ago...
我一朋友在奶头上穿了条钛链
a friend of mine got his nipples pierced with a titanium chain...
一直往下连到他的老二
that goes down and attaches to his Van Johnson.
是不是生日快到了 才让你这么焦躁
Are, are you feeling grumplestiltskin 'cause it's your birthday?
什么
What?
不是
No.
惊喜
Surprise!
算你们走运 我没带武器
Hey, you guys are lucky I'm not armed.
过来
Get in here.
要是六年前 你们就都挂了
If this were six years ago, you'd all be dead.
他下了出租车 你肯定不相信
So then, he gets out of the cab, and you will not believe it.
-你猜我一转身发现了什么 -无线耳机
-I turn around, and what do I find? -AirPods.
-他的无线耳机 -他的无线耳机
-His AirPods. Come on. -His AirPods!
好扯的故事
Crazy story.
-每次都一样 -屡试不爽
-Every time. Come on. -Every single time.
今天有业绩吗
Make any sales today?
明知故问
You know I didn't.
你那什么捕梦网一类的东西有出货吗
Did you sell any dreamcatchers on Etsy or whatever it is that you do?
三天后就该交房租了 韦德 我不可能一直给你垫着
Our rent's due in three days, Wade.I can't keep carrying you.
放心 我还有点钱
Relax. I have the money.
我卖了一些地上捡的过期降压药
I sold some old blood pressure medication I found lying around.
你傻逼吗 想害死我啊
You trying to kill me, motherfucker?
成天拿盐当饭吃的是哪个傻逼
I'm not the one dousing everything in salt, motherfucker.
我每天都祈祷...
I pray every day that...
天降业火烧死你这个混球...
fire finds your body...
替上帝完成...
and finishes the job...
-他没种完成的事 -我好害怕啊
-God didn't have the nuts to do. -That's hurtful.
你看看我的表情就知道我有多害怕了
If you could hear the look on my face, you'd smell how sad I am.
最近有什么好看的吗
You watched anything good?
《英国烘焙大赛》
Great British Bake Off.
我去
Oh, goddamn.
这十年我就靠这节目活着呢
That show stood between me and suicide for ten years.
这是我的感受 主要是对堕胎 宗教自由...
Those are my feelings on abortion, religious freedom...
还有动保 隐私 疫苗...
animal rights, privacy rights, vaccines...
以及市场自由 气候变暖
free-market capitalism, global climate change.
不不 你没台词 巴克
Yeah, duh-duh-duh. No, no speaking lines, Buck.
主演瑞安·雷诺兹同时也是编剧之一 巴克在《死侍2》中被取消台词 一直持续到本片
嗨 雪绪
Hi, Yukio.
嗨 韦德
Hi, Wade.
头套挺真的
Nice fake o'clock shadow.
这是夏日巴黎画染 源自法国
It's a summer balayage. From the French.
犹如夏日天然的灿烂阳光
It's meant to mimic thenatural highlights of the sun.
-就是个假发 -属于高科技植发
-It's a toupee. -It's a hair system.
-我喜欢你的高科技植发 -谢谢
-I love your hair system, Wade. -Thank you.
要不要来点可卡因
Wanna do some cocaine?
凯文·费奇说过可卡因是敏感词 没法过审
Hey, cocaine is the one thing that Feige said is off limits.
-那就叫玻利维亚爽身粉 -他们知道那是同一类东西
-What about Bolivian marching powder? -They know all the slang terms.
他们有一长溜的敏感词
They have a list.
-单板滑雪（吸毒） -蜜桃眼影也不行
-Even snowboarding? -Even disco dust.
-白女向碱走（移魂女郎） -阿甘跌撞撞也不行（阿甘正传）
-White girl interrupted? -Even Forrest Bump.
-鼻屎糖（可卡因） -甜甜圈的糖霜都不准提
-Booger sugar? -I wouldn't even try powdered gonuts.
-堆雪人吗（冰雪奇缘台词） -想
-You wanna build a snowman? -Yes.
但不能播
But I can't.
拉一下试试
Pull here.
-这里吗 -对
-Here? -Yeah.
-怎么了 -这就是好玩的地方
-What happened? -That's the fun part.
谢谢你能来
Thanks for coming.
别客气
Yeah.
工作怎么样
How's work?
我升职了
Oh, I got a promotion.
真的假的
No way.
一个小中层 但我依然很开心
Yeah. It's mind-numbing middle management, but I'm happy.
太棒了
That's great.
-在处对象吗 -你呢
-You seeing anyone? -How about you?
有
Yeah.
是一个同事
A guy from work.
叫德蒙
Dermot.
德蒙
-他人很好 -那就好
-He's kind. -Good.
喜欢爬山
Likes to go hiking.
还没让我中过枪
Hasn't gotten me shot yet.
那也未必
Well, it's early days.
你呢 有对象吗
What about you? You seeing anyone?
没有 我住个一居室 跟瞎子艾尔拼床
No, no, I live in a one-bedroom apartment. I share a bed with Blind Al.
-明白了 -好
-Okay. All right. -All right.
祝你生日快乐
Happy birthday to you
-说两句 -对
-Speech! Speech! -Yes!
好啦
All right. Okay, okay, okay.
过生日
Birthdays.
地球每绕行月球一圈都是新的冒险
Boy, every spin around the moonis a new adventure indeed.
-是太阳 蠢蛋 -好 就你聪明
-Sun, dumbass. -Okay, round-earther.
-我说到哪了 -人生的冒险
-Where was I? -The adventure of life.
对
Right.
这几年过的浑浑噩噩
It's been a challenging few years.
好久没见到大家了
Haven't seen you guys in a while.
有很多经历 有很多改变
Been through a lot, change of life.
-更年期？ -你他妈的不看剧本吗
-Menopause? -Bitch, are you improv-ing?
抱歉
Sorry.
抱歉让你见笑了 雪绪
I'm sorry that you had to see that, Yukio.
没关系
It's okay.
但我还是很快乐
But I'm happy.
这都是
You know, and that's, that's...
因为有你们各位
because of each and every one of you.
我难以形容
I guess, what I'm trying to say is...
我有多么骄傲 多么感激
how proud I am, how grateful I am...
能站在这里
to be standing in a room...
跟我爱的每个人相聚
with every single person I love.
我是世上最幸运的人
I'm the luckiest man alive.
许个愿吧 朋友
Make a wish, buddy.
收到 好朋友
Ten-four, good buddy.
要吹咯
Going down.
韦德·威尔逊？
Wade Wilson?
脱衣猛男 一定是多芬德叫来的
Oh, yeah. Dancers. Dopinder must have ordered you.
这是警察的角色扮演吗
Are those supposed to be cop costumes?
当我没问
Never mind.
开始脱衣服吧...
Take your clothes off...
头盔留着 这不是《风月俏佳人》
but leave the helmets. And this isn't Pretty Woman.
1990年电影 茱莉亚·罗伯茨饰演的妓女 一开始不同意和男主接吻
我们要湿吻
We're kissing. All right?
你们通常用哪首舞曲
What song do you guys normally dance to?
我是不是该表现出害怕来
Is that supposed to be scary?
我不是头一回走后庭
Pegging isn't new for me, friendo.
但迪士尼应该是
But it is for Disney.
后面还没开发那么到位
Okay, I've never been a natural bottom,
所以要前戏做足
so we're gonna take things real slow.
而且眼神要激情交会
And I want some crazy eye contact.
不是你 你
Not you. You.
隔着面具虽然看不见眼睛 但对你有感觉
Can't see your eyes through the mask, but I can feel them.
我们先到走廊上
We're gonna move on down the hallway...
免得事后难打扫
so we can spare a clean up on aisle asshole.
大家意下如何
How does everyone feel about this plan?
-我看你欠收拾 -对 就保持住这个状态
-I don't like you. -Yes. Let's hold on to that attitude.
搞的时候把怒气发泄出来
And we're gonna do it angry.
威尔逊先生
Mr. Wilson...
你刚才无意识中有点失禁了
you appear to have soiled yourself while unconscious.
那是有意识的 你是什么人
I wasn't unconscious. Who are you?
名字叫悖论
I go by the name of Paradox.
你可以称我为悖论先生 这里是TVA
Mr. Paradox. And you're sitting here at the TVA.
时间变异管理局
The Time Variance Authority.
我们是个严密的监控组织
We're really a watchdog organization...
但实际工作内容比听起来要轻松
except we're more lighthearted than that sounds with a sort of...
有些复古讽刺的味道
throwback, ironic twist.
我们负责守护所谓的神圣时间线
And we're in charge of defending what's known as the Sacred Timeline.
我操 我第三部电影竟然塞这么多内容
Holy fuck. That is a shit-ton of exposition for a threequel.
是因为我用过电索的时光机吗
Is this because I used Cable's time machine?
我救了几个人的命 然后就把它毁掉了
Brought a couple of people back to life, then I destroyed it.
-那都是八百年前了 -对
-That was a long time ago. -Yes...
我们知道时间线被你乱改一通
we're aware of your abuse of your timeline.
而且是相当的混乱
And you were so abusive of it.
不过 这次跟那无关
No, it has nothing to do with that.
跟我来
Walk with me.
我带你来是想告诉你
I brought you here, Mr. Wilson, to tell you...
你与众不同
that you're special.
其实你被选中来实现一项更高的目标
In fact, you've been chosen for a higher purpose...
连我都不清楚是什么
a purpose unclear even to me.
但是...
But...
这个目标能把整个神圣时间线
one that could save the entire Sacred Timeline...
从未来的恐怖命运中拯救出来
from a possibly grisly fate sometime in the future...
若没能避免那命运 就需要...
which may very well need to be...
复仇了
avenged.
这个神圣时间线
This Sacred Timeline...
我猜它会跟漫威有关...
I assume I'm going to marvel...
就像...
at how...
一个系列电影？
cinematic it feels?
大量的角色...
Gratuitous cameos...
可以随便客串 甚至全体登场？
indiscriminate use of Variants, the whole package?
你自己看
Well, you tell me.
队长
Cap!
你不会再迷惘了 韦德
You are no longer lost, Wade.
你能成为英雄中的英雄
You can be a hero among heroes.
我们关注你有一段时间了
We've been surveilling you for quite a while.
-地铁站 -时变局前哨站 对
-Subway station. -A TVA outpost, yes.
那是什么
And what is that?
那是我吗
Is that me?
那是索尔吗
Is that Thor?
他在哭吗
Is he crying?
别剧透那么多
Let's not get ahead of ourselves.
那发生在遥远的未来
That happens in the distant future.
-索尔为什么哭 告诉我 -别再问她了
-Why is Thor crying? Quick! Tell me. -Do not speak to her.
打住 看着我
Stop that. Eyes on me.
我带你过来 是为了给你机会
I brought you here to offer you an opportunity.
多年前你曾追求过 但没得到的机会
The opportunity you sought years ago, but for which you were not ready.
我们相信 现在你已经准备好了
We believe you're ready now.
离开你的时间线
Ready for a chance to leave your timeline...
投入最伟大宇宙的机会
and join the greatest universe of all.
我要实现你梦想已久的心愿
I am about to give you the thing you've always wanted.
我懂你的意思
Oh, I smell what you're stepping in.
漫威宇宙的力量即将彻底改变
The power in the Marvel Universe is about to change forever.
我是弥赛亚...
I am the Messiah...
我就是...
I am...
漫威救世主
Marvel Jesus.
失陪一下 马上回来
Can you excuse me for just a moment? I'm just gonna go over here.
死侍这个项目在福克斯可谓阻力重重 瑞安·雷诺兹十余年不懈推进 才有了第一部电影
去你妈的 福克斯
Suck it, Fox!
老子跟迪士尼混了
I'm going to Disneyland.
去死吧
Get fucked!
-在哪签合同 -不需要书面手续
-Where do I sign? -Oh, there's no need for paperwork.
很好 说实话我也不看
Good. Not to brag, but I do not read.
不过我需要一样东西
There is one thing I will need, though.
屌炸天啊
Oh, fuck off!
给我侍奉吧 白胡子
Adorn me, Beardo.
BGM：Fergie - 《Glamorous》
帅他妈的呆
Fucking A!
完美 说一句
It's perfect! FYI...
你们的裁缝真是个禽兽 但我喜欢 合体舒适
your tailor is a predator, but I love it. Snug.
没有骆驼趾
No camel toe.
崭新的味道和艾德曼合金武士刀
New car smell and adamantium katanas?
真是太客气了
You shouldn't have.
别害羞 使劲看
Go ahead. Take it in.
没错 你内裤变更紧了
And yes, your underwear is getting tighter.
那家伙心里很明白
That guy knows what I'm talking about.
他穿着像是个中层
His clothes says middle management...
但眼神里写着中出
but his eyes say fuck-y fuck-y.
对 你看着很不错
Yes. You look very nice.
不错
"Nice?"
这位大哥都快扑上来了
Your buddy here is ready to throw it all away for me.
-打给你老婆吗 -人事部
-You calling your wife? -HR.
你老婆在人事部上班？
Does your wife work in HR?
很高兴你这么满意
I'm really glad you're taking this so well.
何止满意
I'm taking it well.
我一向热爱工作 不过...
I have never had a problem traveling for work. That said...
还是得先讨论一下休假安排
we should talk vacation days.
我喜欢工作一周休息一周
I'm more of a one-week-on-one-week-off kind of guy.
丹麦就是这么干的
I think it's what they do in Denmark.
丹麦的国旗可能永远不会插上月球
You know, you'll never see a Danish flag on the moon, but...
但幸福指数是真的高
goddamn it, they're happy.
启动你这绝版的亚马逊手机
Now, let's power up your little Amazon Fire phone there...
送我回家 我好让朋友知道他们可以晋升为...
and zip me back home so I can let my friends know that they've been upgraded...
我的信徒
to disciples.
我想你还...没搞清楚
I don't think you... quite understand.
你不能回家
You will not be returning to your home...
是因为你将无家可归
because there will be no home to return to.
你说什么
Come again?
说清楚点儿
This time in my ears.
这是你的宇宙 威尔逊先生
This is your universe, Mr. Wilson.
那就是...
That...
宇宙失去锚定者之后的情形
is what happens when a universe loses their Anchor Being.
看到他内部开始崩塌了吗
See how it decays from the inside?
-这就是现实衰亡的过程 -什么是锚定者
-This is how a reality dies. -What's an Anchor Being?
锚定者是至关重要的人物 如果他死亡
An Anchor Being is an entity of such vital importance that when they die...
整个世界就慢慢衰亡直至消失
their whole world slowly withers out of existence.
你中头彩了 因为我还没死
You've just won the lottery because I didn't die.
只是中年危机而已 现在已经好多了
It was just a little midlife crisis. I'm better now.
不
Oh, no, no, no.
-老天啊 -你笑我也笑
-Oh, my God. -Oh, I love to laugh.
你真以为自己是锚定者吗
Can you imagine if you were the Anchor Being?
-是呀 -不是你 威尔逊先生
-Yeah. -No, it isn't you, Mr. Wilson.
你们宇宙的锚定者死了 他牺牲了自我
Your Anchor Being died in an act of self-sacrifice so epic...
悲壮到连时间线都心如刀割
that it sent shivers down the Timeline.
我指的当然是...
I am referring, of course, to...
罗根 金刚狼
Logan. The Wolverine.
别成为他们想要的产物
Don't be what they made you.
原来死亡是这种感觉...
So this is what it feels like...
罗根
Logan.
当然
Of course.
罗根
Logan.
Logan?
手上长叉子的那个
The guy with forks for hands?
那个金刚狼
That Wolverine?
懂了
Yeah, I got it.
现在把他死去的画面一关 就阻止他死去了
You can turn your retro graphics of death off now. Make it stop.
我们没去阻止 也根本阻止不了
We're not doing it, Mr. Wilson. We certainly can't stop it.
那我们还剩多少时间
How long have we got?
一般情况 还剩几千年
In most cases, couple thousand years.
-那还好 -一般况其实不够快
-Well, sweet. -Well, most cases aren't fast enough.
对我来说
Not for me.
什么意思
What does that mean?
就是说我是被派来负责...
It means that I have been tasked...
监督你的宇宙终结
with overseeing the end of your universe.
不管高层的人想用哪种处理方式
And regardless of what the pencil pushers upstairs would prefer...
我不会...
I will not...
浪费生命盯着一个司空见惯的衰亡过程
waste my life watching it die slowly of natural causes.
我们以前都是直接删掉 干净俐落
We used to just prune these things. Simple.
优雅又高效 但现在的时变局
Elegant. Efficient. But I'm told the TVA...
已经不允许那样了 但我喜欢
doesn't like to do that anymore. Well I do.
不管所谓的高层怎么说
And no matter what my so-called superiors say,
多元宇宙不需要保姆
the multiverse does not need a babysitter.
而是需要一个慈悲杀手
We need a mercy killer.
在现在这个状况下
And in this instance...
我就是那个慈悲杀手
I am the mercy killer.
那是干什么用的
What in the MacGuffin is that?
那是时间开膛手
That's a Time Ripper, Mr. Wilson.
一个加速装置
An accelerant.
启动它
Once completed,
就能直接摧毁你们宇宙的时空矩阵
it will allow me to destroy the spacetime matrix of your universe.
我不想只是个给时变局打工的
You see, I don't want to work for the TVA.
我要成为时变局
I want to be the TVA.
首先得让这个组织的老家伙们明白
And the first step involves showing this organization...
有很多手段可以提高效率
how much more efficient it can become.
就是说 我会让你的宇宙快速慈悲地终结
To wit, I will be giving your universe a swift and compassionate end.
放心 你的朋友不会有什么痛苦
And don't worry, your friends won't feel a thing.
结束时就像这样 那是什么
It'll be over just like this. "Oh, what's that?"
相信我
Trust me.
《老黄狗/Old Yeller》：迪士尼1958电影 男主最后一枪结束了狗狗痛苦的生命
我的整个世界 你想一枪给它解脱了？
You're gonna Old Yeller my fucking universe?
用你们的说法 是的
In your parlance, yes.
两枪胸口一枪头：即莫桑比克射击法 在《疾速追杀》系列电影中大量出现
两枪胸口一枪头
Two in the heart, one in the head.
威尔逊先生 你现在有两个选择
Look, Mr. Wilson, you have two choices.
一是重回心爱的人身边 陪他们一起消失
You can either rejoin your loved one sand collectively cease to exist in...
而《疾速追杀1》的导演大卫·雷奇 同时也是《死侍2》的导演
可能还剩72个小时 或者...
I'd say, seventy-two hours. Or...
加入神圣时间线
you join the Sacred Timeline.
结束你无足轻重
And you end your days of insignificance...
平凡无奇的日子
and mediocrity.
韦德
Wade.
韦德 你终于
Wade, you can finally...
终于可以
finally,
有作为了
matter.
那才是我真心想要的
That's all I've ever really wanted.
我知道
I know.
我一贯的道德底线就是没有底线
And you know I'm, I'm nothing if not morally flexible.
好
Yep, yep.
我愿意
I'll do it.
明智的选择 神圣时间线欢迎你加入
Wise choice. The Sacred Timeline's happy to have you.
我不只要找到金刚狼 还要打断你的鼻子
I was actually talking about finding the Wolverine and breaking your fucking nose.
BGM：The Goo Goo Dolls - 《Iris》
去找他 快去找他
Find him. Find him!
他确实找到了
And boy, did he ever.
所以我们回到了开始那一幕
Which brings us back to this.
继续亵渎这具神圣遗体
The desecration of the sacred corpse.
老天啊
Oh, my God!
我操 我的胳膊
My own fucking arm!
这才像话
Now we're talking!
不是这样
Not like this!
不 老天爷啊
No, dear God! No!
抱歉 金刚狼的爪子真的很难驾驭（双关语 hard亦有硬的意思）
I'm sorry! Wolverine-ing is hard!
快住手
Make it stop!
指《金刚狼3》的导演詹姆斯·曼高德
曼高德尽力了
Mangold tried.
你这个人渣
You sick fuck!
罗根是位英雄
Logan was a hero.
是加拿大唯一有价值的名字
And the only thing worth a shit to ever come out of Canada.
此处台词模仿了第94届奥斯卡颁奖典礼上 威尔·史密斯扇耳光事件
别从你那臭嘴里出现我国家的名字
Get my country's name out of your fucking mouth.
还有我的剑 给我
And my sword. Give me that.
我得再找一个罗根才行
Oh, I gotta find me another Logan.
一个活蹦乱跳的
An alive one.
不必送了 我自己离开
Don't get up, guys. I'll see myself out.
罗根
Logan!
我需要你跟我走一趟
I'm gonna need you to come with me.
什么人
Who's asking?
死侍用hairy替换了玛丽·卢·雷顿（Mary Lou Retton）名字中的Mary 形容对方体毛旺盛
看看这毛丽·卢·雷顿
Oh, look at this little Hairy Lou Retton.
这是收尾的一跳吗 小家伙
Did you stick the landing, little guy?
玛丽·卢·雷顿为美国体操运动员 身高只有1米45 调侃了漫画中金刚狼1米6的身高设定
落地很稳
Yes, you did!
还真是还原漫画
Comic accurate short king.
这么袖珍的迷你金刚狼
Such a cute wittle Wolvie.
赶紧他妈的转场
Cue the fucking montage, baby.
啊嗬 真是一片火海
Ahoy. Everything seems to be on fire.
天启时代金刚狼 出自地球-295 漫画中因与镭射眼的战斗失去了左手
有喷火龙吗
You have a dragon?
你一看就是锚定者...
You have Anchor Being written all over...
BGM：Huey Lewis & The News - 《The Power Of Love》
独眼金刚狼出自1988年漫画 帕奇是金刚狼在马德里坡调查时的假名 patch亦有眼罩的意思
帕奇
Patch!
这才像话
Now we're talking.
哦耶
Oh, yeah.
简直是六边形数值
That's the whole goddamn package right there.
你好啊
Howdy!
我在寻找锚定者
I'm just... I'm auditioning Anchor Beings.
暮狼寻乡金刚狼 电影《金刚狼3》就是以该漫画为基础改编的
你得抹点椰子油了
Yeah, that's gonna need some coconut oil.
金刚狼被钉在X架子上的场景 还原了漫画《非凡X战警》251期封面
这他妈什么情况
What in the fuck?
你还好吗
Are you okay?
对 对
Oh, yes, yes.
约翰·伯恩经典的棕色战衣
Classic John Byrne brown and tan.
金刚狼在漫画《无敌浩克》180期首次登场 并与浩克在森林中对战
我记得你穿着这身大战浩克
Now, you fought the Hulk in this outfit. No?
爪子反射出浩克的脸 还原了《无敌浩克》340期封面
我可是漫威救世主 你个笨蛋 我...
I'm Marvel Jesus, you dull creature, and I will not...
不是找你 我只是碰巧路过
It's not you. We're just going in a different direction.
从后面看 你有点像亨瑞...
You know, from behind, you look a little bit like Henry...
哎我操
Oh, my fuck!
该金刚狼由亨瑞·卡维尔饰演 也就是DC宇宙中超人的扮演者
卡维尔狼
The Cavillrine.
传说是真的
The legends are true.
先生 我想代表全人类说
And may I say, sir, on behalf of all humanity...
就是这个感觉
this just feels right.
那些一手好牌打稀烂的片商 待遇绝对比不上这里
We will treat you so much better than those shit fucks down the street.
你最好马上滚蛋
You were just leaving.
还不行 我那个宇宙的命运正...
No, sir. Not while the fate of my universe is at...
这个看着有希望
This one looks promising.
睡你的吧
Down you go.
满上
Again.
我说过 这里不欢迎你
I told you. You're not welcome here.
你到哪都不受欢迎
You're not welcome anywhere.
马上给我滚出去
Now get the fuck out of my bar.
再来一杯我就走
Just give me one more drinkand then I'll leave.
少来这套
That's not how it works.
等等 酒留下
It does now. Leave the bottle.
我认识你吗
I know you, bub?
不认识 但我认识你
Nope. But I know you.
大家都认识我
Everybody knows me.
我是金刚狼
I'm the Wolverine.
没错 你是
Yes, you are.
而且我需要你立刻跟我走
And I'm gonna need you to come with me right now.
小妞 我没兴趣
Look, lady, I'm not interested.
-你还真喝醉了 -我为啥跟你走
-Really getting into your cups here. -Why would I go with you?
因为 很不幸...
Because, unfortunately...
我需要你...
I need you...
更不幸的是我整个世界...
and even more unfortunately, my entire world...
需要你
needs you.
你们要打炮还是打架
You two gonna fuck or fight?
这你也忍得了？
You gonna take that from him?
对
Yep.
我也看出来了
I can tell you have a sort of...
我再靠近你 就会伤我的心
don't-get-too-close-I'll-only-break-your-heart vibe going here...
反正现在哪个金刚狼都会伤我 不止心
but every other Wolverine would've really hurt me by now.
而且我有点赶时间 抬腚 走了
And, I'm sort of on the tick-tick. So upsy-daisy. Here we go.
起来 我扶你 大个子
Up you go. I got you, big guy.
狼爪不举了
Whiskey dick of the claws.
-年过40的金刚狼 正常 -别逼我
-It's quite common in Wolverines over forty. -You don't want this.
没错 你也别逼我
You're right. I don't. And you don't want this.
【枪口】笑一个 等闪光灯
除非你想自己脑袋开花
Unless you wanna take a deep breath through your fucking forehead...
否则我劝你三思
I suggest you reconsider.
走吧 小狼狗
Let's go, peanut.
等一下
Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
看好了
Watch this.
好 那
All right. That...
别激动
Easy.
妈呀
Good God.
酒蒙子还没喝够
Thirsty little honey badger, aren't ya?
没关系 你继续
It's okay. Keep going.
反正观众习惯注水烂片了
Audiences are accustomed to long run times.
果然醉倒了
Guess you'll have to do.
好 走吧...
Okay, here we...
看看这件睡衣
Look at those jammies.
只等了他妈20年
That only took twenty fucking years.
锚定者来了
One Anchor Being coming right up!
注意左侧 小宝贝
On your left, baby girl.
从2000年第一部《X战警》提到黄色战衣（1小时9分32秒处）到本片上映间隔了24年
这个罗根无所不能 连歌舞片都能演
This Logan has the same he-can-do-anything-even-musicals look.
更棒的是...
And bonus...
他一直穿着战衣 可见他多么想再演一次超英电影
he's actually wearing a costume like he's not embarrassed to be in a superhero movie for once.
我没明白
I don't understand.
你说我的宇宙正在衰亡
You said my universe is dying...
就是因为这个蠢蛋害自己挂了
because this sack of nuts got himself killed.
现在问题搞定了
Well, problem solved.
天啊
My God.
你以为锚定者可以随便换吗 尤其是他
You actually think you can replace an Anchor Being with this?
我本来也不会接受其他金刚狼的 但你...
I wouldn't have accepted any other Wolverine BT dubs. But you...
也挺能耐的 找到最烂的一个金刚狼
have outdone yoursel fand brought me the worst Wolverine!
什么叫最烂的一个
What do you mean, the worst one?
威尔逊先生
Mr. Wilson.
这个金刚狼让他的整个世界失望
This Wolverine let down his entire world.
他也算传奇 带引号的
He's the stuff of legend, but not in a good way.
他的作为
And what he did...
应该说...
well...
有些事就是无法原谅
some things are just beyond forgiveness.
好吧
Okay.
我该如何补救 你要我怎样都行
How do I... How do I make this right? I'll do anything.
我给你一个大展身手的机会
I gave you a chance at greatness.
是因为我的高层认为你与众不同
Because my superiors deemed you special.
显然 也是带引号的
Clearly not special in a good way.
似乎你有更重要的未来去创造
Apparently you have some important future purpose to serve.
索尔 他抱着我哭
With Thor. He holds me.
我仁至义尽了 前程似锦的机会我给了
But, I did my duty. I gave you the opportunity to be somebody.
你非但不感激我的提议
And instead of accepting my offering with humility and gratitude...
还打断我的鼻子
you broke my nose.
-看着没事 -你还把一位英雄的遗体挖出来
-It looks great. -And you decimated dozens of my men...
干掉我几十个手下
with the exhumed corpse of a hero.
同时羞辱了他的遗体和记忆
Dishonoring not only his remains but his memory.
你是网络喷子吗
What are you, the Internet?
你的世界注定要毁了
Your world is dying!
感谢
Thank you very much.
没有办法阻止
And there's no stopping it.
比较人道的做法就是
The humane thing to do...
长痛不如短痛
is to make it quick.
我的宇宙崩塌 会激发你的食欲？
Is the thought of vaporizing my universe making you peckish?
-我是发泄出来 -我即将失去珍惜的一切 都是因为
-I'm eating my feelings. -I'm about to lose everything that I've ever cared about...
这个垃圾中的战斗鸡
because that hairy thunder cunt from down under cunt...
最终死掉了 他就站在我身后对吧
finally dies and he's standing right behind me, isn't he?
欢迎加入漫威电影宇宙
Welcome to the MCU, by the way.
《复联4》之后 不考虑索尼的蜘蛛侠系列 漫威仅《银河护卫队3》一部电影质量优秀
现在正赶上低谷的时候
You're joining at a bit of a low point.
至于你 我要告诉你的领导
As for you, I wanna talk to your boss.
现在打电话 跟他 她或他们说
I want you to get him on the phone and you tell him, her, or them...
漫威救世主不陪你们玩了
that Marvel H. Christ isn't playing.
见鬼
Holy shit.
我刚刚感觉到所有人都菊花一紧
I just heard a symphony of buttholes clenching all at once.
你越权了
You're off grid.
你老板还不知道你在这里乱搞
Your bosses don't know what you sick fucks are doing down here.
告诉你 论事儿逼 我是当中的战斗逼
Well, I'll tell you what. I have a black belt in Karen...
我要到楼上
And I'm gonna go upstairs...
找你们领导好好说道说道...
and I'm gonna tell them all about you and your...
耳根子清净多了
Silence is nice, isn't it?
他哪去了
Where the fuck did he go?
垃圾堆 很适合你去
To the trash heap. You'll fit right in.
好险
That was close.
画面左侧纸张上的图案 是2015年漫画《秘密战争》第5期封面
纸上的饮料瓶 是08年电影《无敌浩克》中 斯坦·李喝过的那款饮料
别在那傻站着
Don't just stand there, you ape.
拉我一把
Give me a hand up.
算了 我没事 非常感...
Nope. I'm actually okay. Thank you very much...
画面右上角是加拿大国家电视塔 因瑞安·雷诺兹是加拿大人 《死侍》系列一直都有加拿大元素
这什么鬼地方
Where the hell are we?
不知道 看着像疯狂的麦克斯
I don't know. Looks kind of Mad Max-y.
那样就侵犯版权了吧
But that would be IP infringement, right?
还在嘴贱
Fucking jokes.
画面最前方是雷神漫画中的头盔与美国队长早期的三角形盾牌
操 操
Fuck! Fuck.
你刚刚有没有在听
Were you even listening back there?
如果不回去找悖论先生那傻逼...
If we don't make it back to that Mr. Paradox asshole...
我认识的每个人都会死
everyone I know is gonna die.
关我屁事
Not my fucking problem.
你还会说别的吗
Oh, is that all you got?
你那世界完蛋的时候 也是这么说的吗
Is that what you said when your world went to shit?
再说一遍
Come again?
我都听见了
Yeah, I heard all about you.
你搞砸了一切
How you screwed up everything.
你该感谢我救你脱离苦海
You should be thanking me for pulling you out of that bed you shit in.
你这背后捅刀的王八蛋
You back-stabbing son of a bitch!
进入贤者模式了吗
Are you ready to be calm now?
【二十世纪福克斯】
安息吧 福克斯
Rest in pieces, Fox.
我不想跟你动手 小狼狗
I don't want to fight you, peanut.
不管你过去是什么样
Doesn't matter what you did.
我只需要你现在帮忙
I just need your help.
老子不管你的破事儿
I don't fucking care.
操 看着就肉痛
Fuck. This is gonna hurt.
算了
All right.
去他妈的
Fuck it.
把观众们想看的端上来
Let's give the people what they came for.
决一死战
Let's fucking go.
准备好专用的那只手 宅宅们
Get your special sock out, nerds.
可以开冲了
It's gonna get good.
BGM：AC/DC - 《Hells Bells》
中招
Gotcha!
小刀宝
Baby Knife!
看你的头怎么长回来
Let's see you grow your fucking head back.
等一下 可以补救
Wait, wait, wait! I can fix it!
-可以补救 -补救什么
-I can fix it. -Fix what?
不管你做了什么
Whatever it is that you did.
不管造成了什么后果
Whatever made you so bad.
你也听到时变局那些混蛋说的了
Those, those pricks in the TVA. You heard him.
他们有办法终结我的宇宙...
They have the power to end my universe...
但也有能力改变你的宇宙
but they also have the power to change yours.
我们回去...
We get back there...
就可以逆转...你的世界
and we can fix your world. Together.
我保证
I promise.
他们能做到
They can fix it.
自相残杀 我们就输了
We fight each other, we lose.
天啊 是他
Dear God, it's him.
谁
Who?
这时候
The one.
通常会出现一位人气超高
The superhero equivalent to comfort food, or Molly.
由白人一线大牌出演的超级英雄
White guys' answer to all the disappointments. And another A-lister.
提前告知
Fair warning, gorgeous.
你会听到一些不雅词汇...
You're going to encounter some indelicate language...
少许后庭娱乐 但我们被禁止...
a smidge of ass play, but we've been prohibited...
在镜头前使用可卡因
from using cocaine. On camera.
他们来了
They're coming.
他们是谁
Who's "they?"
最前面是神奇四侠漫画中的飞行车
红骷髅在《美国队长1》中的座驾 但车标和涂装却是钢铁侠
跟狂暴飞车似的
Oh, they're driving angry.
标准的超级英雄落地
Now that's a superhero landing.
让我来
I got this.
队伍中间的蛋糕车 是出自剧集《月光骑士》
跟紧我
Stay close.
是 队长
Aye, aye, Cap'n.
你可以的
You got this.
把你们抓回去 卡桑德拉一定会很高兴
Cassandra is gonna be giddy when she sees what we caught.
你们跑不掉的
You can't run.
众所周知
Everybody knows that.
你有看到谁要跑吗 蠢货
You see anyone running, dick for brains?
等一下你就笑不出来了
You're not gonna love what happens next.
上帝啊
Oh, my God.
天呐
-天呐 他要说了 -你他妈
-Oh, my God, he's gonna say it. -Fuck.
-上帝啊 他要说了 -说什么
-Oh, my God! He's gonna say it! -Say what?
复仇者 集结...
Avengers, assemble...
-燃烧吧 -什么
-Flame on! -I'm sorry, what now?
我操啊
Fuck!
我们不认识他
We don't know that guy.
我们以为认识
We thought we did.
我认得你
I know you.
哇操...
Holy...
剑齿虎
Sabretooth.
你老哥
Your brother.
准备受死了吗
Ready to die?
等一下 暂停
Wait, wait, wait! Time!
这副模样可不行
You look ridiculous.
观众等这场对决几十年了
People have waited decades for this fight.
绝不轻松 小刀宝
It's not gonna be easy. Baby Knife.
连续攻击 把他干倒
Shoot the double, you take him down.
侧身发力 一肘制敌
Side control, then full mount...
全身压上 强敌断气
and you ground and pound till he makes no sound because he's dead.
给我闭嘴
Shut the fuck up!
上帝啊
Oh, my God!
祝你好运 我是狂粉
Okay. Good luck. I'm a huge fan.
怎么了 妹子
What is it, girl?
忘了带卫生巾吗
Is there trouble at the well?
麻烦大了
Big trouble.
看
Behold!
你们高贵女王的头颅
The head of your precious queen...
狂暴女神
Furiosa!
我有金刚狼
I have the Wolverine!
她听我号令
I alone control her!
对我不敬...
You come for me...
就是向她宣战
you come for her.
抱歉 应该是 他
So sorry. I know it's pronounced "him."
我性别盲 是我的错
I'm gender blind. It's my cross to bear.
下一个是谁
Who's next?
蛤蟆人
Toad!
你上
You're up.
我操
Fuck.
雷神
God of Thunder.
我睡了多久
How long was I asleep?
某个部位没睡着
Not all of you was asleep.
别费劲了
Don't bother.
他们手法很老道
They're very thorough.
我们到底在什么地方
If you know where we are, start talking.
这里是虚空
You're in The Void.
可以把它看作炼狱
Think of it as purgatory.
里德（神奇先生）称它为超现实废料场
Reed called it a metaphysical junkyard.
也就是处理各种垃圾的地方
Where anything useless goes before it gets annihilated forever.
或者说 时变局处理多元宇宙中不守规矩者的地方
And where the TVA sends people that don't play nice with the rest of the multiverse.
-比如你 -还有你
-Like you? -And you.
被什么处理
What does the annihilating?
艾利奥斯
Alioth.
这片还有艾利奥斯？
Alioth is in this thing?
洛基第一季第五集那个？
From Loki, season one, episode five?
这里每个人都在躲艾利奥斯
Everyone here is on the run from Alioth.
大多没能成功
Most don't make it.
不过还有反抗势力
There's a resistance, though.
就是像我们一样得以幸存的人
Other people like us that managed to survive.
他们躲在边境 想设法离开
They're hiding out in the borderlands, trying to find a way the fuck outta here.
那我们就去边境
Then that's where we go.
我们？ 团队吗
"We?" Us? A team?
我愿意 一言为定
The answer is yes. Shake on it.
操 划到我了
Fuck! You nicked it.
你那罗小刀前端顶到我了
Just got the tip with your little steak knife.
那些人能帮我们回到时变局
These "others" can help us get back to the TVA.
然后改变现状
Make them fix things.
笑个屁 老兄
Something funny, bub?
她可能不会同意
She might have something to say about that.
她是谁
Who's "she?"
在虚空中
In The Void...
你不是艾利奥斯的大餐
you're either food for Alioth...
就是她的奴隶
or you work for her.
漫画《暮狼寻乡》中也曾出现巨大的蚁人尸体 位于皮姆十字
1969年生人的保罗·路德在好莱坞经常被调侃"不会变老"
保罗·路德终于见老了
Paul Rudd finally aged.
看来红坦克换你这个版本了
You must be this year's Juggernaut.
-谢谢 -劝你闭嘴
-Thank you. -I'd keep your voices down.
她不喜欢废话多的家伙
She don't like the chatter.
她会爱死你的
She's gonna love you.
那是...查尔斯吗
Is it... Is that Charles?
教授 是我们
Chuck! It's us!
那不是查尔斯
That's not Chuck.
见鬼
Ah, shit.
残障歧视 好政确
Oh, ableism. Great.
那些白左觉醒的变态可就不高兴了
That's not gonna go over well with the woke mob.
金刚狼
A Wolverine.
我还在想何时能抓到一个
I wondered when I'd get one of you.
你是X战警
You're one of Xavier's.
你认识查尔斯？
You-You know him? You know Chuck?
认识
Oh, I knew him.
来自同一个子宫
We shared a womb.
源自漫画《新X战警》的情节 两人胎儿时期的争斗还造成了母亲流产
娘胎里我就想用脐带勒死那个奸诈小鬼
Tried to strangle the sly little fellow with my umbilical cord.
对啊 我也不喜欢室友 还是个瞎子
Amen. I've never loved roommates. Mine's blind.
但她能看见可卡因
Except she can see cocaine.
因为某种原因...
For some...
搭个话 陛下 我没词了
reason. You want to chime in, Your Majesty? I'm dying here.
你是谁
Who are you?
查尔斯的孪生妹妹
Charles Xavier's twin,
卡桑德拉·诺瓦
Cassandra Nova.
-放屁 -我可能有点松
-Bullshit! -I was an anal birth.
你们俩真有爱
You two are cute.
感觉这样更不错
I have a good feeling about this.
你这只小萤火虫让我抓了好几年
And I've been trying to catch this little firefly for years.
对不对 强尼
Haven't I, Johnny?
这可不是该去认识小朋友的时间
Aw... You picked the wrong time to make new friends.
强尼跟我们介绍过你
Oh, Johnny told us all about you.
-快闭嘴吧 -是吗
-Maybe shut up now. -Yeah,
-还是别... -聊聊天而已
-maybe don't... -We're just talking here.
强尼说你是妄自尊大的傻逼神经病
Yeah, Johnny told us you're a psychotic megalomaniacal asshole.
他说的 不是我
His words, not mine.
沉迷于支配和痛苦
Hellbent on domination and pain.
-你是这么说我的？ -不是
-You said all that about me? -No!
不是
No!
-我根本没说过 -硬气点儿 强尼
-I don't... I didn't say any of that! -Sticks and stones, Johnny!
别让她吓倒
Don't let her intimidate you.
就像你在车上说的
It's like you said in the convoy.
这个行尸走肉一般的嗜血妖女
This finger-lickin' dead-inside pixie slab of...
青石板胸豆奶稀
third rate dime-store nut-milk...
只适合舔他翘臀里面的原味菊花
can eat your delicious cinnamon ring...
事后再一路滚回她那秃顶的地狱
and kick rocks all the way to bald hell.
我这辈子根本没说过这些话
I have never said any of those words in my entire life!
别谦虚
The modesty.
都以为我嘴贱 但跟他一比...
People think I'm a shit talker. But this guy...
小巫见大巫
Next level.
什么 这... 我...
What? This... I... We...
我都听不懂那是什么意思
I don't even know what half of that means!
-这什么... -我佩服得五体投地 真的
-This... I... What? This... -My hat's off to you, sir. Truly.
我没... 他在... 那是...
I didn't... He's... That's...
我没有...
I don't...
MUC中共有三位演员名叫克里斯 分别为克里斯·埃文斯（美国队长与霹雳火）
不是我最喜欢的克里斯
Not my favorite Chris.
你这个蠢蛋 你把他害死了
You stupid piece of shit. You just got him fucking killed!
克里斯·海姆斯沃斯（雷神） 克里斯·帕拉特（星爵）
我也很伤心
We're all grieving!
你知道他片酬有多高吗
PS, do you know what he was doing to the budget?
艾利奥斯饿了
Alioth is hungry.
应该有点误会
There's been some kind of mistake.
旁边这个大金毛是候补锚定者
Big yellow is a back up Anchor Being...
我是漫威救世主 私下也可以叫我MJ
and I'm Marvel Jesus. MJ, if you're nasty.
你可能觉得有点难听 有另一个英国的狗东西
This may be hard to hear, but there's another British villain...
想摧毁我的宇宙 我要阻止他
who's gonna destroy my universe and I'm gonna stop him.
你看着可不像拯救世界的料
Oh, honey, you don't really strike me as the world-saving type.
说到痛处了？
Did I hit a nerve?
我本来不想这么说
I didn't want it to come to this.
要么你配合我们
Either you help us...
否则我哥们儿这就唱一部《乐器推销员》
or my friend here is gonna sing the entire second act of Music Man...
完全不用暖嗓准备
with zero warm-up.
那张椅子哪来的
Where'd you get the chair?
偶尔也有查尔斯进来
Well, once in a while, I do get a Charles through here.
但没有与我同一宇宙的
Never mine, though.
反正
No.
他也不想来找我
He didn't care to find me.
Z世代就爱自怨自艾
Gen Z and their trauma-bragging!
你就不能跟我们一样 化悲愤为力量
Can't you just stuff it down, turn it into accomplishment...
或者憋出癌症来吗
or cancer like the rest of us?
我跟你们不一样
But I'm not like the rest of you.
或许金刚狼除外
Except maybe the Wolverine.
我们联手将令人闻风丧胆
Now, we could be truly terrifying together.
你有那么强
You're that scary, huh?
时变局肯定这么认为
The TVA certainly thought so.
因为我还不会走路 他们就送我过来了
They sent me here before I could walk.
那也是我最难忘的人生际遇
And you know, it's the best thing that ever happened to me.
我爱这里
I love it here.
你住在垃圾场里
You live in a garbage dump.
我们都知道谁才住在垃圾场里
I think we both know who lives in the garbage dump.
虚空对于我宛如天堂
The Void is a paradise.
我能在这里施展全部力量而不受制约
I can wield my power here without shame.
可惜没有查尔斯·赛维尔教我压制这股力量
Unfortunately I had no Charles Xavier to teach me temperance.
你的查尔斯呢
What about your Charles?
他有保护你吗
Did he protect you?
让你感到安全吗
Did he make you feel safe?
我们是变种人 永远不会安全
We're mutants. We're never safe.
我不想打架
I don't want the smoke.
我跟你无冤无仇 我只想救我朋友
I don't have any beef with you. I just want to save my friends.
我...我想回家
I just... I want to go home.
我倒是能送你回家
Well, the thing is, I could get you home.
-太好了 -问题是我不想
-Good. -But I don't want to.
不太好
Not good.
你想要什么 韦德·威尔逊
What do you want, Wade Wilson?
你的...
Your...
手指进来了 但没有快感
fingers are inside me, but not in a good way.
我哥用念力就能进入别人的脑袋
My brother could enter one's mind with a thought.
我只能弄脏我的手
I have to get my hands dirty.
让我来
I've got you.
让我来...
I've got you...
什么意思
What do you mean?
我没法和你沟通 你心思不在这里
I can't, I can't reach you. You're not here.
我整个人都在这
I'm right here.
-你没有 我没法... -我没想别的
-No, you're not. I can't... -I'm right here.
你得用行动来证明
Then show me. You got to do something.
证明什么
Show you what?
证明你不只在乎你自己
Show me you care about something bigger than you.
你被他们拒绝后 就在自暴自弃
Ever since they turned you down, you took a knee.
宝贝 你始终没振作起来
Baby, you never got back up.
我知道你很痛苦
I know you're going through something.
让我陪你
Let me go through it with you.
我们疯味相投
Your crazy matches my crazy.
你在想什么
Where'd you go?
天啊
Oh, my God.
你就说出来吧
You just say it. Okay?
说你不要我
Say, "I don't want you.
你不想跟我在一起
"I don't want to be with you."
说啊 快说
Go ahead. Say it. Say, say, "I don't..."
快说 你不想跟我在一起
Say it. You don't wanna be with me.
说出来我就走 说你不要我
Tell me that and I'll walk away. Say, "I don't want you."
见鬼
Fuck...
你永远不会有什么作为
You'll never fucking matter.
什么
What?
你永远不会有什么作为
You'll never fucking matter.
你...
You'll...
永远不会...
never...
有什么...
fucking...
作为
matter.
她没说过这句话
She never said that.
没有
No.
但我敢说她是这么想的
But I bet she thought it.
你好恶毒
You are so mean!
我脑袋也尝到了 你手上有仇恨的味道
My brain could taste your fingers, and they tasted like hate!
亲密协调员主要负责激情戏 医疗检查等情节拍摄时 协调演员安全地身体接触
剧组的亲密协调员死哪去了
And where in God's name is the intimacy coordinator?
你深陷迷惘 威尔逊先生
You're so lost, Mr. Wilson.
早在你来之前就如此
And long before you came here.
这是小刀宝 它会日穿你那个逼脸
This is Baby Knife. She's gonna fuck you in the face now.
想杀我 这么一个小刀可不够
If you want to kill me, it's going to take more than a little blade.
六个呢
How about six?
兄弟够猛
My boy's wicked strong.
好兄弟
That's my big boy.
就是你
Yes, you are.
有点意思
Well, this has been fun.
但现在 需要给大家伙喂饲料了
But the big guy needs to eat and the rent is due.
对了...
By the way...
你们就是饲料
you're the rent.
快啊 操
Come on! Fuck!
你走不走
You coming or what?
来了
Coming!
你在想什么
What you thinking 'bout?
放开我
Get the fuck off of me!
马上就好了
Almost done.
什么马上就好
Almost done what?
你的两瓣屁股把我的刀都夹住了 茎肛狼
Getting my knife out of your buttocks, pervert!
操
Fuck!
停止你的意淫
Get your mind out of my pants!
-我告诉布蕾克 -从现在开始
-I'm telling Blake. -New rules.
你别说话
I talk now.
-那观众肯定不答应 -给我闭嘴
-That's gonna be very hard on the audience. -Shut the fuck up!
让我想想
Let me fucking think.
我们得回去找悖论 对吧
Now we gotta get back to Paradox, right?
对吧
Right?
意思是
It's an excuse.
-我又可以说话了吗 -点头就行 混蛋
-Am I allowed to speak now or... -Just nod, asshole.
好
Right.
那就去找强尼这倒霉孩子被你害死之前...
Then we find the others that poor kid Johnny was talking about...
-提到过的幸存者 -还倒霉孩子 他都快50了
-before you got him killed! -"Poor kid." He's like fifty!
出生于1981年的克里斯·埃文斯 本片上映时已43岁
如果他们知道离开的方法 就得找到他们
Yeah, if there's a chance they know how to get out of here, we find them.
让时变局能逆转我的过去 这是你保证的
And make those TVA fuckers fix my shit like you fucking promised!
我闻到了你的决心
I smell quest.
我闻到了食物
I smell food.
你最终是因为什么穿上正版战衣的
So what made you finally wear an honest-to-God costume?
我穿红色是因为别人看不出我流血
Mine's red so they can't see me bleed.
我知道黄色也很实用
But I could see how yellow would be useful too.
你测过多动症吗
Have you been checked for ADHD?
但我得过几种花柳病 应该是多动症引起的
But I've had several STDs, which were probably caused by ADHD.
操
Fuck!
你到底找什么
What are you looking for?
【外用酒精】
谢了
Thank fuck.
那可是医用酒精
No, no, no. That's rubbing alcohol.
不能喝的... 好家伙 肝脏不要了
You don't want to drink... Oh, yeah. There you go. Fuck that liver.
好吧
Good. Okay.
那些是什么
What the fuck are those?
平常我都戴假发 但没人看出来
Back in civilian life, I wear a toupee, but nobody knows.
都能看出来
Everybody knows.
能不能聊聊你的过去 还是...
Wanna talk about what's haunting you, or...
等第三幕放几个闪回镜头
should we wait for a third act flashback?
滚你妈的
Go fuck yourself.
事实上...
You know...
在我的世界里 你...
in my world, you're...
你很伟大
You're well regarded.
在我的世界可不是
Yeah, well, not in mine.
我在我的世界也不招人喜
They don't like me much in mine either.
看得出来
You don't say.
我想有一番作为
I wanted to be something, you know. I...
我想当复仇者
Shit, I wanted to be an Avenger.
-去他妈的复仇者 -嗯哼
-Fuck the Avengers. -Yeah.
我没被录取 X战警也是
I didn't make the cut, though. Same with the X-Men...
-我女朋友离开我时... -你还有女朋友？
-When my girlfriend left me and then I just... -You had a girlfriend?
对
Yeah.
凡妮莎
Vanessa.
刚认识时她是舞女
When we met, she was a dancer.
我们生活美满
We had a whole life.
很幸福
It was good.
可是我...
But, oh, boy, I just...
却搞砸了
Fucked that right up.
而你
But you.
你是X战警
You were an X-Man.
还是头号X战警
Fuck that. You were the X-Man. You...
金刚狼
The Wolverine.
他在我的世界曾是英雄
He was a hero in my world.
是吗
Yeah, well...
在我的世界 他什么都不是
he ain't shit in mine.
你说罗根曾是英雄 怎么回事
You said, "Logan was a hero." What happened?
他死了
He died.
怎么死的
How?
可以这么形容 胸膛被一棵树捅穿
Well, technically, you were chest-fucked by a tree, but...
其实是你为了救人耗尽了生命
really, you just ran out of batteries trying to save someone.
救谁
Who?
一个女的在实验室制造了她 给她取名X-23
The shitheels that grew her in a lab called her "X-23." But...
但她只是个孩子
she was just a kid.
像你的减龄缩小版 但出手更狠毒
A younger, daintier, some how meaner version of you.
你就是为救她而死
You died trying to save her.
很感人
It was beautiful.
听着 朋友 我知道你有痛处
Look, mijo, I know you're hurting.
我那非裔瞎子室友艾尔常说
My blind, elderly, African-American roommate, Blind Al, always says that...
痛苦使我们认清自己
pain teaches us who we are.
有时我们得直面痛苦 而非一味逃避
Sometimes we need to listen to that pain instead of running from it.
-我靠 -她很有智慧
-Holy shit. -Yeah, she's wise.
不 你叫她瞎子艾尔
No, no, no. That's her name? You call her "Blind Al?"
她就是瞎子
Well, she's blind.
BGM：Chris De Burgh - 《The Lady In Red》
瞧瞧你
Look at you!
它想跟我们一起走
She's coming with us.
-它并不想 -不 它想的
-No, she's not. Fuck no! -Oh, yes, she is.
-她想... -抱歉
-Oh, yes... -Sorry!
不好意思
Sorry about that!
过来 宝贝
Come here, girl!
你是谁
Who are you?
我是死侍
Oh, I'm Deadpool.
我猜你也是死侍
And I guess you're Deadpool too.
Nicepool扮演者写的Gordon Reynolds 源自一个瑞安·雷诺兹自己采访自己的节目
在这里大家叫我斯文侍
But in here, everybody calls me "Nicepool."
等你看到女死侍的时候 相当正点
Oh, my goodness. Wait till you see Ladypool. She is gorgeous.
她刚生完宝宝
She just had a baby too. And...
但完全看不出来
Can't even tell.
这么说不太合适吧
I don't think you're supposed to say that.
没关系
That's okay.
我自认为是女权主义者
I identify as a feminist.
这样
Right.
那是镀金的点50口径沙漠之鹰手枪吗
Are those gold-plated,.50 caliber Desert Eagle pistoleros?
当然
'Course.
跟我的耳环很搭
To match my ear huggie.
能送我吗
Can I have them?
除非我死了
Over my dead body.
你真幽默
You're fun.
你们已经见过玛丽·普汀了
And I guess you've already met Mary Puppins.
漫画中的狗侍曾被化妆品公司用于非法实验 获得了愈合能力并变得非常丑陋
也就是狗侍
AKA Dogpool.
小心别乱摸
Careful where you put your hands.
她全身上下都是G点 一碰她就起反应
She's ninety percent g-spot, and she'll let you know it.
演员狗狗名叫佩吉 2023年获得"英国最丑狗狗"的称号
这条色狗只要一离开你的视线
You let this little flirt out of your sight for one second and...
就开始黏个新干爹
she starts shopping for a new papa.
如果你驾驭不住她 也许是你配不上这只小可爱
If you can't be a responsible pet owner, then maybe you don't deserve this little unicorn.
完全认罪 法官大人
Guilty on all charges, Your Honor.
我保证下不为例
Shan't happen again.
你干嘛这么有礼貌
Why are you so nice?
礼貌又不花钱
Oh, it costs nothing to be kind.
把嘴闭上一样是免费的
Shutting the fuck up is also free.
好温馨的建议
caliente
这是罗根
This is Logan.
他以前经常光膀子 但离婚后就变了
He's usually shirtless, but he's let himself go since the divorce.
此处指休·杰克曼于2023年9月宣布离婚
你的头套呢
Where's your mask?
瑞安·雷诺兹在2010年被《人物》杂志选为"全球最性感男士" 休·杰克曼在2008年也获得过此头衔
我这帅脸
Come on, guys.
真受不了
Ugh, this guy.
我们在找一批幸存者
We're looking for a group of survivors.
我知道
Oh, they're out there.
但良心建议 你们最好别碰上死侍军团
Yeah, but merc to merc, you better hope that you don't run into the Deadpool corps.
他们是群疯子
Yeah, they're crazy.
漫画《惩罚者屠杀漫威宇宙》中 惩罚者曾将死侍分尸埋在不同地点 防止其愈合
会把你碎尸万段 埋在虚空各角落
They will chop you up into a thousand pieces and hide you all over The Void.
他们刚走出童年噩梦
If they could only process their childhood trauma...
积聚的怨恨正无处发泄
they'd go on one heck of a healing journey.
我们要去边境
Look, we're headed for the borderlands.
知道在哪吗
You know where it is?
就在正西12公里 我的车可以借你们
Yeah, that... That's twelve klicks due west. I can lend you my ride, if you like.
这是我的荣幸
It would be my honor.
不行 绝对不行
No, no, no. Absolutely not.
搞什么... 不行
Uh-uh. What the... No! No!
快点上车
Just get in the car.
这不是车
This isn't a car.
这是本田他娘的奥德赛
This is a Honda fucking Odyssey.
油门反应垃圾
Throttle response sucks a cock.
过时的中控
Dated infotainment system.
当本田发现性病再度流行...
When Honda saw that untreated chlamydia was making a comeback...
他们就出了奥德赛 看谁更恶心
they invented the Honda Odyssey to compete.
快他妈给我上车
Get in the fucking car.
它会送你平安抵达
She'll get you there safe and sound.
老贝琪从不掉链子
Old Betsy always does.
你得把狗还给我了
You're gonna have to give me my dog back, though.
我知道 听好了 孩子
I know. Listen. Yes, child.
如果你想放弃它 或它需要新家
If you ever wanna give her up, or if she needs a new home...
或是你有什么三长两短
or if something should happen to you...
我乐意当它的新爸爸
I'd love to be her papa.
我会有什么三长两短
What would ever happen to me?
多着呢
Lots of stuff.
-天啊 -不 我们要私奔
-Jesus. -No! We're running away.
-给我 -玉米长得太密了
-Give me that. -The corn was too dense, girl!
-抱走 -过来
-There. -Come here!
-妈的 -你好啊
-Fuck! -Hello!
拜拜
Bye.
BGM：Avril Lavigne - 《I'm With You》
随便问问
Okay, I'm just gonna ask...
你这套战衣穿着怎么样
What's with the suit?
反正我行动之后的第一件事...
First thing I did when I flamed out...
-就是把这身脱了 -别说了
-I took mine off. -Drop it.
你的就没那么丑
It's not that ugly.
-别再逼逼战衣了 -你自己做的吗
-Stop talking about my suit. -Did you make it yourself?
-我这件就是 -安静
-Been there. -Quit. Now.
X战警要求你穿的？
The X-Men make you wear it?
那些狗娘养的
Those sons of fucking bitches.
他们不是真朋友 我就敢说
They are not your friends, I'll tell you that.
真朋友不会让你...
Friends don't let friends...
穿着个实习生T恤出门打击犯罪
leave the house looking like they fight crime for the Los Angeles Rams.
给我闭嘴 不然...
Shut the fuck up about this, or...
别发火 狼兄弟
Watch your frown lines, angel baby.
-我也是想培养咱们之间的感情 -那就聊点别的
-I'm just trying to bond a little bit. -Yeah, well, then talk about something else.
好
Fine.
别闹了
Stop it.
如果他们能逆转你的世界...
If they can fix your world...
等你离开这里后 第一件事要做什么
what's the first thing you're gonna do when you get out of here?
去喝医用酒精 或者玻璃水？
Get some rubbing alcohol shots, maybe a wiper fluid chaser?
你说什么
What did you say?
等你回去 最想做什么
I said when you get back, what's the first thing you're gonna do?
不 前面一句
No, no, no. Before that.
如果他们逆转了你的世界
If... they can fix your world?
什么叫 如果
What do you mean, "if?"
-就是... -你他妈骗我
-I mean... -You lied to me.
你根本不知道他们能不能改变过去 是不是
You don't have a fucking clue if they can help me fix things, do you?
不 我是说...
No. I, I mean...
操 操 我没骗你
Fuck! Fuck! I didn't lie!
-你骗我 -没有 我画了个合理的饼
-You lied! -No! I made an educated wish!
因为我需要你的帮助
Because I need you.
原因...就在这里
This. This is why. Right here.
如果不想办法 他们会死
'Cause if we don't do something, they die.
我对拯救世界一窍不通
I don't know anything about saving worlds.
我又为什么这么在乎
And why would I even care?
因为我整个世界就在这照片里
Because my entire world is right here in this picture.
就是这九个人
It's only nine people...
我不知道自己该怎么去救他们
and I have no idea how to save it alone.
我只是拿钱帮人消过灾 但你...
I know how to fuck people up for money. But you...
你知道怎么救人
you know how to save them!
至少另一个金刚狼知道
At least the other Wolverine did.
操 看来我确实找了最烂的金刚狼
Fuck! I guess I'm stuck with the worst one.
你说你画了个...
Did you say you made...
他妈合理的饼
an educated fucking wish?
人们都叫我嘴炮佣兵
They call me "The Merc with the Mouth."
可不是叫我...
They don't call me...
加拿大绝赞深喉的老实孩子
"Truthful Timmy, the Blowjob Queen of Saskatoon."
你再说
One more word.
再多说一个字
Please give me one.
思想品德
Gubernatorial.
操
Oh, fuck!
你他妈就是个笑话
You know what? You're a fucking joke.
难怪你当不了复仇者
No wonder the Avengers didn't take you.
还有X战警 他们可是来者不拒
Or the X-Men. And they'll take fucking anyone.
你根本就是...
I mean, you are...
可笑 幼稚 脑残的白痴
a ridiculous, immature, half-wit moron.
我就没见过...
I have never met...
比你更可悲...
a sadder...
只会耍嘴皮子 洋相百出的蠢蛋
more attention-starved, jabbering little prick...
一辈子都没见过 这说明什么 我他妈活了...
in my entire life. And that says a lot, 'cause I've been alive...
两百多年 现在就告诉你...
for more than two hundred fucking years, and I'll tell you...
那光头娘们儿说得很对 你这玩意儿拯救不了世界
that bald chick was right about one thing. You will never save the world!
你连跟脱衣舞女的感情
You couldn't even save a relationship...
都拯救不了
with a goddamn stripper!
妈了个逼的 我倒是盼着你凄惨的死在外面...
And motherfucker, I wish I could say you'd die alone...
老天最大的笑话就是你竟然死不了
but it's one of God's best jokes that you can't die...
还让别人跟着倒霉
except that's on all of us!
你这嘴炮怎么没词了
Oh, you got nothing to say, Mouth?
我要跟你干一架
I'm gonna fight you now.
是吗
Oh, are you?
BGM：The Greatest Showman Ensemble - 《The Greatest Show》出自电影《马戏之王》
BGM：The Greatest Showman Ensemble - 《A Million Dreams》出自电影《马戏之王》
BGM：John Travolta, Olivia Newton-John - 《You're The One That I Want》
怎么不逼逼了
Not talking now, are ya?
你个贱人
You dirty bitch.
不 不
No, no, no!
小刀宝
Baby Knife!
我收回我的话 本田奥德赛质量够硬
I take it all back. The Honda Odyssey fucks hard.
可惜你不是 金针狼
Too bad you don't, needle dick.
好戏才刚刚开始
Oh, we're just getting started, bub.
你...妈了个...
Oh, you... Fuck!
不同宗教的标志组成了单词coexist（共存） 意为摒弃分歧 和平相处
《奇异博士2》中位于万达格山的雕像
这张怪兽头骨的床是电影《雷神3》中 浩克在萨卡星的那张床
索尔
Thor!
我们在哪
Where are we?
不知道 但我喜欢这里
No clue, but... I like it here.
好
Okay.
看看你们
Look at you... all.
你们一定是那些人
You must be the others.
好极了
Terrific.
温故知新一下 你是...
So just to refresh, you are...
-神奇女侠 -艾丽卡 -果然是艾丽卡
-Wonder... Elektra? Yes. -Elektra.
当然记得
Who could forget?
至于你
And you.
没想到会在这见到你
I was not expecting to see you here.
我以为你已经...
I thought you were, you know...
退休了
retired.
退学？
Retarded?
退休
"Retired."
已经在虚空里了 不想虚得只剩空
I'm already in The Void. I'm not trying to get canceled again.
我不喜欢你
I don't like you.
韦斯利·斯奈普斯与瑞安·雷诺兹曾共同出演2004年电影《刀锋战士3》 据说当时两人有些矛盾
你也没喜欢过
You never did.
这个让我相形见绌的老鲜肉是谁
And who's this succulent reminder of my own inadequacies?
瞧瞧你
Look at you.
就像有超能力的鹰眼
You look like the superhero version of Hawkeye.
我叫雷米·勒博 里米·艾蒂安·勒博
The name's Remy LeBeau, Le Diable Blanc.
你可以叫我牌皇
But you can call me the Gambit.
有阵子没看法国片了 再说一次
It's been a while since I've seen Sling Blade. Hit me again.
大家叫我牌皇
They call me the Gambit.
福克斯早在2014年就宣布要制作《牌皇》的电影 但直到被收购也未能开拍
真的？ 是不是自己特别想当牌皇...
Do they? Are you sure you didn't just really, really want them to...
但一直都没能实现
but it never quite worked out?
还从没有金刚狼在这出现过
You know, we never had a Wolverine up in here.
但我可以教你个基本礼貌 在喝光我的酒之前
But I can tell you now, it's just a common courtesy to ask...
应该先跟主人问一句
before you drink up all of my liquor.
我也不鸟你 省得你教
Well, it's a good thing I don't give a fuck.
妈的
Fuck.
太丢脸了
So embarrassing.
我们大老远来找你们三人
Well, now that that's settled, look, we came a long way to find you three.
我们有四个人
There's four of us.
四个人 是万磁王吗
There's four... Hey, wait. Is it Magneto?
我和蔼的老天爷 一定要是万磁王...
Dear sweet God in heaven, let it be Magneto...
-因为他... -他死了
-because with him... -He's dead.
操 迪士尼竟然在这里省钱
Fuck! Now Disney gets cheap?
就像匹诺曹把脸卡在我屁股里 呐喊着自己是个炮机
It's like Pinocchio jammed his face in my ass and started lying like crazy.
你好骚啊
Ooh, you nasty!
这小红帽 裆下过着没羞没臊的性福生活
Mon petit rouge. Laissez les bons temps rouler, huh?
完全没听懂 你到底是干嘛的
Not a single word. What do you do exactly?
给纸牌赋能 然后来个炸裂效果
Charge the playing cards and make them go boom!
你的能力是近景魔术 很棒
Your power's close up magic. That's good.
我们胜券在握了
We're not totally fucked at all.
谁带我们来的
So who brought us here?
是我
That would be me.
希望我不后悔
Don't make me regret it.
靠
Holy shit.
罗根 是她 X-23
Logan. That's her. That's X-23.
X-23衣服上的"savage"是致敬漫画《野蛮复仇者》 成员包括金刚狼 艾丽卡 蛮王 惩罚者等
就是我跟你说的那个
She's the one I told you about.
你们怎么会困在虚空里
Hey, how did you all get stuck in The Void?
一天有人敲门
There was a knock at the door.
-时变局把我扔到这 -我也是
-TVA sent me here. -Me, too.
也许我就是在这里出生的 很难讲
Well, maybe I was born here. It's, it's hard to know for sure.
时变局判定我们的宇宙即将毁灭
TVA decided our universe was dying.
我连最后斗争的机会都没有
And I never even got a chance to fight for it.
因为我们不会保持沉默
People like us don't go quietly.
时变局很清楚这一点 直接不给我们机会
TVA knows that, so they took us out.
我愿意 我加入
The answer is yes. I'm in.
-加入什么 -团队
-In what? -A team.
我 你 你 和我 大家齐心协力
Me, you, you, and me. All of us together.
-一起离开这鬼地方 -别听他的 他是个...
-Let's get the fuck out of this place. -Don't listen to him. He's...
-狗日的骗子 -那是合理的饼
-a fucking liar! -It was an educated wish!
听着
Look.
我们去过卡桑德拉的基地
We've been inside Cassandra's lair.
只有通过她才能离开虚空
The only way out of The Void is through her.
她能让我们回去
She can get us home.
-她亲口说的 -等一下 你们去过她的基地？
-She told us. -Wait a minute, you've been inside?
-还活着出来？ -胡扯
-And you made it out alive? -Bullshit.
-没人能做到 -我们做到了
-Nobody's ever done that. -We did.
每次我们有人对抗她...
Every time one of us has gone up against her...
全都死了
they die.
惩罚者 快银 夜魔侠
The Punisher, The Quicksilver, The Daredevil.
夜魔侠 真遗憾
Daredevil? I'm so sorry.
詹妮弗·加纳与饰演夜魔侠的本·阿弗莱克于2018年离婚 所以艾丽卡这样回应
-没关系 -好吧
-It's fine. -Okay.
就连心地善良的强尼·斯通也是
Even that sweet, baby angel, Johnny Storm.
他离开还没多久...
He up and gone missing like...
差不多两天前
what, two days ago?
太可惜了
That's so sad.
不管这位强尼在哪 他会没事的
Wherever this Johnny fella is, I'm sure he's thriving.
人多好办事 我们两个
Look, there's, there's strength in numbers. All right? Us...
再加上你们 我们能击败卡桑德拉
plus, you guys. We can put Cassandra over our knee...
逼她让我们离开虚空
and force her to let us out of The Void.
我很了解自我怀疑的感觉
I know what it means to feel self-doubt.
-我没那感觉 -我好得很
-I don't feel that at all. -I'm good.
就像肚子里有条嗨起来的寄生虫
Gnawing at your gut like a coked-up tapeworm.
你说出了我的心声
It's like you're holding up a mirror to my soul.
也许你们没能拯救自己的宇宙
You guys may not have been able to save your universes.
但你们可以为它复仇
But you can avenge them.
这也是强尼所希望的
It's what Johnny would have wanted.
等等
Wait.
你见过强尼？
You knew Johnny?
没错
Oh, yeah.
这蠢蛋忽悠着他一起走...
Dickhead here talked him into a team up...
结果强尼确诊为挂了
and Johnny came down with a little case of the deads.
不不 说不准的
No, no, no. We don't know that.
只是点皮肉伤 可能还活着
It was just a flesh wound. He may have survived.
就算活着 他也宁可死掉
If he survived that, he is praying for death.
-谢谢金刚狼医师 -快说
-Thank you, Doctor Wolverine! -Spill it!
你把强尼怎么了
What'd you do to Johnny, huh?
再不说我就动手了
Talk or I'm gonna start dealing.
好 好
Okay. Okay.
是这样
Look.
他对卡桑德拉满嘴跑火车
He ran his fat-ass mouth about Cassandra.
然后她抬手就扒掉了他的皮...
Then she zip-zapped his skin...
内脏散落到地上...
leaving his organs to splash crudely onto the ground...
血液渗进土里 景象让人不寒而栗
while the soil greedily drank his blood. It was horrible.
他就像我的兄弟一样
He was like a brother to me.
既然他壮志未酬身先死...
Look, he died before he could make a difference. But...
或许你们救不了你们的世界...
Look, maybe you couldn't save your worlds, but...
但是 你们能挽救我的世界
but Jesus Christ, you can save mine!
我并不在乎你的世界 不过...
I don't give a shit about your world, but...
如果这两个都能活着出来 或许我们联手...
if these two made it out of there alive, maybe together...
就能杀进去 合力干掉她
we can get back in. And take her down.
在我老家
Where I come from,
那叫自杀 亲爱的
we call that suicide, Chere.
只要封住她的读心能力 我们就有机会
If we can block her psychic powers, we can get a leg up. I know it.
我知道万磁王死了
Now I know Magneto's dead.
但我敢说他的头盔...
But I'd venture to guess that his helmet...
-还在某个地方... -卡桑德拉烧熔了那头盔
-is lying around here somewhere... -Cassandra melted the helmet.
-操 -在她杀了他之后
-Fuck! -After she killed him.
操
Fuck!
她要以绝后患
She don't play.
她知道那头盔是唯一能屏蔽她能力的东西
She knows that helmet was the only way to protect anyone from her powers.
红坦克的头盔也有同样效果 但是...
The only other helmet that strong is Juggernaut's, but...
-他们是一伙的 -红坦克的头盔 就是它了
-he works for Cassandra. -Juggernaut's helmet. That's it.
不过想要把那顶头盔摘下来
Yeah, and we done be knowing that lid ain't coming off...
-只有砍下他的头 -抱歉 帅哥
-without that dome gonna come off wit'it. -I'm so sorry, beautiful.
冒昧地问一句 你这口音是跟谁学的
I want this to be gentle. Who is your dialect coach?
小黄人吗
The Minions?
感觉我们都没找对剧本的中心思想
I feel like we are missing critical exposition here.
我受够了 受够了躲藏
I'm sick of this shit. I'm sick of hiding.
我们的世界早已忘了我们
Let's face it, our worlds forgot about us.
或根本不知道我们
Or never learned about us.
我们曾是英雄
The heroes we were.
曾经拯救众生
Lives we saved.
或曾想去拯救
Or wanted to save.
也许这两个人就是我们的机会
Maybe these two are our chance.
至留名青史
To be remembered.
我们原本的道路
The way we deserve.
对味儿了
Yes.
原本的结局
An ending.
-成为传奇 -对
-Legacy. -Yes!
听听大哥说的
Yes! Let this man cook.
这才是该有的样子
This is what I'm talking about.
大场面动作戏加慢镜头 配上悲壮的音乐
Big slow-motion fights, sad music.
所有人并肩作战 出生入死的那种
Everybody working together. Who knows if you live or die? That sort a thing.
-都准备好了吗 -随时出手
-Who's ready? -I was born ready.
爽 牌皇？
Yes! Gambit?
我没见过我父亲 但我被射出屌的那刻就准备好了
I ain't know my daddy, but I'm sure I shot out of his dick ready.
天啊 真有画面感
Jesus Christ, that is graphic.
当时老爸给老妈把蛋都塞进去...
Yeah. He was laying them buttery nuts all up in my mama...
我一冒出头就说 你好啊哥们儿
and I shot out there and I said, "What's up, Doc?"
强尼跟你肯定很铁 X-23 你呢
Johnny must have loved you. X-23, what's it gonna be?
我叫劳拉
The name's Laura.
-跟他们决一死战 -决一死战
-Let's fucking go. -Let's fucking go!
-别让人看扁了 -对
-It's on like chicken and corn. -Yeah!
-就这么干 -你们都他妈死定了
-We're doing this. -You're all fucking dead.
我靠 刚才多好的气势
My God! Read the room.
我不想跟人说话 回去吧
I'm not looking for company. Get out of here.
你让我想到他
You remind me of him.
爱生气 醉醺醺 凶巴巴
Angry. Drunk. Mean...
-听起来不错... -还没讲完
-Sounds like a great guy... -Wasn't finished.
在最关键的时候从不缺席
Showed up when it mattered the most.
没有什么能阻挡他
Couldn't help it.
你可能没意识到 但...
You might not know it, but...
你是个好人 罗根
you're a good man, Logan.
你可能没意识到 很明显 我是最糟糕的罗根
You might not know it, but apparently, I'm the worst Logan.
因为你 我才能活下来
I got to have a life because of you.
因为你 我才能长大
I got to grow up because of you.
很多孩子也是这样
A lot of kids did.
但是很多孩子因为我 才无法长大
A lot of kids didn't grow up because of me.
相信我 小鬼 我不是你想象中的英雄
Trust me, kid, I'm no hero.
这套战衣说你是
That suit says different.
喜欢吗
Yeah. Do you like it?
斯科特总想让我穿上这一身
Scott used to beg me to wear it.
还有琴 暴风女 野兽
So did Jean, Storm, Beast.
他们都是
All of them.
他们要我加入团队 我当时还不肯
They wanted me to be part of the team, but I wouldn't.
我说他们看起来很可笑
Told them they all look fucking ridiculous.
其实...
I mean...
我不想让他们知道我想加入
I couldn't have them thinking I wanted to be there.
有天我一个人出去 那天 人类来了...
And then one day, while I was off on my own, the humans came...
开始猎杀变种人
and went mutant hunting.
剩下的我猜得出来
I can guess the rest.
不 让我...
No, no, let me...
让我说出来...
Let me say it. I...
我需要说出来
I need to say it.
等我醉醺醺地回去 为时已晚
By the time I stumbled home shitfaced from the bar, it was too late.
他们死了 全死了
They were dead. Every...
只有这套战衣能提醒我 他们是谁
This suit's all I got to remind me of who they were.
提醒我做了什么
And what I did.
我们天亮出发去找卡桑德拉
We're headed to Cassandra's at sunup.
一路顺风 我不参与
Have fun. Not my fight.
少了你不会成功的
We won't pull this off without you.
不管你以为我是谁 你找错人了
Whoever you think I am, you got the wrong guy.
你本来就不是我要找的人
You were always the wrong guy.
【午餐肉】
什么事
What?
艾利奥斯没解决他们
Alioth didn't get them.
卡桑德拉想先自己陪他们玩
Cassandra wanted to play with them herself first.
结果他们逃掉了
They got away.
-他们找到其他人了？ -没有
-Did they find the others? -No.
那就好
Good. All right.
是其他人找到他们
The others found them.
你说话真风趣 火人 一点也不俗套
Oh, very cute. Well done, Pyro. Classic bait and switch.
-被你的幽默感折服了 -放轻松
-You really got me there. -Relax.
如果他们和诺瓦开战 都会被她搞定（诺瓦是卡桑德拉的中间名）
If they come after Nova, she'll handle it.
卡桑德拉疯起来无人可挡
Cassandra is a lunatic wild card.
你以为我们为什么把她放在这
Why do you think we put her there in the first place?
幸好她自己没想要离开虚空
Thank God she's never chosen to leave The Void.
时间开膛手再几小时就能启动了
The Time Ripper is hours away from completion.
我不能冒险
I can not take any chances.
你是不能
Well, maybe not.
但我可以
But I can.
只要钱到位
For a price.
-你声音怎么一直怪怪的 都生理不适了
-Why do you have to say it in that silly voice? It's so icky.
不行就拉倒
You want it done or not?
好 就听你的
All right. Your price.
干掉她
Take her out.
该死的变种人
Ugh. Mutants.
BGM：T.I. - 《Bring Em Out》 该歌手参演了前两部《蚁人》电影
看那边
Ooh! Look at that there!
就是那双大手 从没有人想冲进去
You see them biggum hands come closed. Ain't not a wonna getting up inside there.
牌皇想说的是...
I think what Gambit's trying to say is...
想拿到红坦克的头盔可不简单
getting Juggernaut's helmet ain't gonna be easy.
我瞎编的...
I'm just making stuff up at this...
-镜头对准刀锋战士 -上炮
-Yeah. Tilt up to Blade. -Gun!
这宝贝哪弄来的
Where'd he get that little beauty?
惩罚者的AT4火箭筒
That's Punisher's AT4.
五版惩罚者应该是指四个真人版与一个动画版
哪个惩罚者 已经有五个版本了
Which Punisher? There's been like five of them.
但只有一个刀锋战士
There's only been one Blade...
而且永远只有这一个刀锋战士
and there's only ever gonna be one Blade.
新版刀锋战士由马赫沙拉·阿里出演 原计划2023年11月3日上映 但至今尚未开机
敌袭
Incoming!
目前马赫沙拉·阿里仅以声音形式 在《永恒族》片尾彩蛋中出现
这下有得爽了
Ooh, this is gonna be good.
知道这一刻我等了多久吗
You know how long I've been waiting for this?
今天要一战成名了
I'm about to make a name for myself here.
恐怕你们没办法全身而退
I don't think you guys walk away from this.
你们只要把今天的一切告诉人们
You just make sure people know what happened here today.
出去之后别忘了敬我一杯
And when you get out of here, you have a drink for me, yeah?
你们不必在意敌人 找机会突围
You just stay on our six and get inside.
我们会拿到那件东西
We'll make sure you get the package.
和我们原本的结局
And we'll get our ending.
砰
And boom!
这句话出自《刀锋战士1》中的经典台词
总有傻逼急着上来送死
Some motherfuckers still trying to ice skate uphill.
你们俩逃掉也就算了
You two escaping, I could live with.
竟然又主动跑回来
But coming back? Willingly?
男人就是蠢
Boys are so silly.
我只想回家
I just need to get home.
恐怕没这个选项
Well, that's not on the menu, I'm afraid.
要么战死要么奴隶 二选一
It's death or enslavement. A la carte, of course.
举高高
Upsy-daisy.
总算...
Finally...
可以换个人唠会儿
it's nice to give someone elsea chance to talk.
恕我直言
Not my strong suit.
你就要后悔了
You shouldn't have done that.
再见了 混蛋
Adiós, pendejo
你就是有点特别的那个吧
You are an interesting one, aren't you?
我能感觉到你被他那些洗脑...
I do feel like you get lost behind all of his...
死侍在虚空里随处可见
Deadpools are a dime a dozen here in The Void.
但你...
But you...
这里到底有什么
What's going on in here?
有意思...
Interesting...
出乎我意料
Not what I expected back here.
在愤怒的背后
Behind the anger.
你在逃避
You're hiding.
逃避他们
From them.
逃避那些对你失望的人
From all the ones you let down.
真痛苦
So much pain.
我一走了之
I walked away.
他们挽留我
They called after me and I...
我却一走了之
I walked away.
我总是如此
I always do.
-罗根 -我知道
-Logan! -I know.
不止这些
That's not all you did.
对吗
Is it?
你最后找到他们
You found them.
X战警
The X-Men.
都死了
Dead.
尸积如山
Piled like wood.
然后你做了什么
What did you do?
我开始杀戮
I started killing.
停不下来 也不想停
And I couldn't stop. I didn't wanna stop.
他们都该死
All those bad men.
并没有这样结束
It's not just the bad ones.
我的小野兽
My little animal.
因为我 全世界都敌视X战警
And I turned the whole world against the X-Men.
刀锋战士
Blade!
只有这一次
Just once...
我想成为查尔斯期盼的样子
I wanna be the man that Charles thought I was.
罗根
Logan...
在虚空里 你就是原本的样子
in The Void you can be what you are.
我只想自由
I just wanna be free.
我能给你自由
I can set you free.
我能让所有嘈杂归于寂静
I can silence all those voices.
我来助你
I've got you.
解脱一切
不用
No.
我抓住你了
I got you.
拿下来
Get it off!
送我们回家 不然把你这秃头拧下来
You're gonna send us home, or I'm gonna twist your fucking head off.
你笑什么
Why are you laughing?
戴着这东西 我没法送你们回去
I can't send you home unless you get this thing off my head.
但只要你摘了它
And as soon as you do that...
我就把你们的脑浆蒸发到原子级...
I'm going to boil your brains on an atomic level...
听着恩雅的专辑套装 玩着自己的欢乐豆（恩雅暗喻圣洁的声音）
whilst flicking my bean to the Enya box set.
恩雅还有专辑套装？
There's an Enya box set?
要么弄死两位
Either you kill me...
要么被两位弄死
or I kill you.
两种选择都不赖
Both wonderful options.
要我动手吗
You want me to do it?
不 我自己来
No, I'll do it.
她脖子就在我手里
I have her neck right here.
-方便的很 -你办不了
-It's really no problem. -You'll screw it up.
得了吧 除了最后一部 你全系列PG-13（辅导级）
Oh, come on, Mr. PG-13, except the last one!
搞什么鬼
What the fuck?
你没尝过那种滋味
You have no idea what it's like!
日复一日 与人为奴
Day after day. Shovel the shit.
摇尾乞怜
Fetch the meats.
我几乎已经...
I have spent my entire...
轮不到你说话
Not everyone gets a speech.
她快死了
She's gonna die.
好 如果我摘掉头盔...
Okay. If I take this helmet off...
-你保证不杀我们 -操
-do you promise you won't kill us? -Fuck!
我保证...
I promise...
第一个先杀你
I will kill you first thing.
怎么这么个玩意儿
Why are you like this?
我也想知道
I wish I knew.
摘下来
Take it off.
-什么 -摘下来
-What? -Take it off.
-为什么 -快摘下来
-Why? -Just take it off.
-这是拯救我们世界的唯一机会 -摘下来
-This is our only chance to fix our shit! -Take it off!
我穿着这套战衣
I am wearing this suit.
它有着很多意义 但最重要的是...
And that means a lot of things, but most of all...
它代表我是X战警
it means I'm an X-Man.
我了解你哥
And I know your brother.
尽管我很想杀了你...
As much as I want to fucking kill you...
身上每根骨头都想杀了你...
every bone in my body wants to fucking kill you...
但他决不会让我站在这看着你死
he would not let me stand here and watch you die!
把手放开
Take your hands off.
这是为了他
This is for him.
为了查尔斯
This is for Charles.
不 不 不 我不想变成强尼那样
Hey, no, no, no! Don't you dare do me like Johnny!
我哥爱你
My brother loved you.
他爱我们大家
He loved all of us.
感觉一定很好
Must be nice.
他也会爱你
He would've loved you, too.
如果他知道你的状况...
If he knew about you...
如果他知道你在哪...
if he knew where you were...
哪怕把宇宙开个洞 他也会带你回家
he would've torn a hole in the fucking universe to bring you home.
这就是我的家
This is my home.
那至少让我们拯救他的家 他的世界
Well, then at least let us save his.
想听一件离谱的事吗
You want to hear something crazy?
前阵子有个三流魔法师来过
An amateur magician rolled through here a while back.
当然 被我弄死了
I killed him, of course.
还把他的皮穿在身上了四天
Wore his skin around for four days.
可是...
But...
我发现这个...
I found this...
一件小饰品
little trinket...
这枚悬戒与以往出现过的不同 上面镶嵌了现实宝石与时间宝石
在他的手指上
on his lovely fingers.
奇异博士
Strange!
-漫威星火之环 -那是什么
-Marvel sparkle circle. -What is that?
是你们回家的路
This is your way home.
我是该报答救命之恩 但还想来点好玩的
I do owe you for saving my life. But let's keep things interesting.
艾利奥斯吞掉你们之前 只有四秒钟
I'd say you have about four secondsbefore you're Alioth's food.
快跑
Race ya.
BGM：Jimmy Durante - 《I'll Be Seeing You》
【DriveMax车行】
我们有标准的 三年整车全包
And as I said we've got a standard three-year bumper to bumper warranty.
很高兴你们给我第二次机会
Glad you gave us a second chance.
放心
And don't worry.
韦德和我一组 他也有一半业绩...
Wade and I are a team, so I'll see he gets half the commission...
感觉是起亚
That feels like a Kia.
是起亚嘉华吧
It's a fucking Kia Carnival, isn't it?
哇塞
Holy shit.
那是死侍
That's Deadpool.
-那是金刚狼 -正确答案
-And that's Wolverine. -You're damn straight it is.
福克斯让他死了
Fox killed him.
迪士尼让他复活 逼他拍到90岁
Disney brought him back. They're going to make him do this 'til he's 90.
走吧
Let's go.
我帮你打下班卡
I'll clock you out!
一直如此
Forever!
永不改变
Forever.
起床咯
Wakey-wakey.
上帝
God?
你给我肚子吃了这么多子弹
Now you put all these bullets in my belly...
我要查出原因
and I'm gonna find out why.
我自己招
I'll just say it.
你用把手指伸进来
You don't have to stick your fingers in me.
天啊 问一句就行
Jesus, just ask sometimes.
好
Fine.
真的
Really?
双手插兜
Hands in pockets.
有个人叫悖论
Guy named Paradox.
他说能让我离开虚空
He said he'd get me out of The Void.
我只知道他在时变局工作
All I know is he works for the TVA.
时变局
The TVA.
我们有约在先
We had an agreement.
恐怕那家伙不会守约
I don't think this guy cares.
他会的
He will.
各位
Hey, people!
时间开膛手还要多久才能启动
How much longer before the Time Ripper is active?
还剩最后的安全检查
We're running the final safety checks.
好 辛苦了 雷夫
Okay. All right. Thanks for all your hard work, Ralph.
-慢慢来 -真的吗
-Take your time. -Really?
你说呢 蠢蛋
No, you drooling boob!
情况紧急
No! We have company.
取消安全检查 直接启动
Cancel the safety checks. We need to be live now!
真是一群蠢猪
I hate you so much.
【地铁服务目前暂停】
停 站住
No! Stop!
快滚吧 你们已经迟了
Piss off! You're too late.
-你要完蛋了 -索尔究竟为什么哭
-You're fucking done. -Why was Thor crying?
你们胆子够肥的
How dare you!
还没人能从虚空回来
No one comes back from The Void.
去跟卡桑德拉·诺瓦说吧
Tell that to Cassandra Nova.
悖论 我们有麻烦了
Paradox. We have a problem.
悖论
Paradox.
你比火人想象中的形象白净一点
Well, you are doughier than you looked in Pyro's head.
你想让我死
You tried to kill me.
我还真不清楚这...
I literally have no...
擒王不成 反取其祸
You come for the king, you better kill the king.
欢迎体验颅内高潮会所 悖论
Welcome to the skull fuck club, Paradox.
你也知道她不洗手的
You know she doesn't wash that hand.
这是什么
What's this?
时间开膛手
A Time Ripper?
-小坏蛋 -我们知道
-Naughty boy. -Oh, no. We're on it.
正要去拆了那玩意儿
We're gonna head down and dismantle that thing now.
这有我们 你专心拨弄手指吧
We got ya, boo. You just keep playing those keys.
我不想摧毁它
I don't want to destroy it.
我要利用它
I want to use it.
一边玩去 大人们有话要说
Now, shoo. Mummy and Daddy are having a conversation.
其实 可笑的是什么...
You know, the funny thing is...
我在虚空里原本很快乐
I was happy in The Void.
你送垃圾给我 我和艾利奥斯负责清理
You sent your trash to me. Alioth and I cleaned it up.
各取所需 皆大欢喜
Everyone was happy.
但你非要到我的地盘撒尿
And then you had to go and piss on my side of the fence.
就得当面跟你算账了
And so now the fence must come down.
我要利用你的时间开膛手
I'm going to use your little Time Ripper.
摧毁这个宇宙...
And I'm going to destroy this universe...
以及下一个 再一个 再下一个...
and the next and the next and the next...
直到只剩虚空为止
until all that's left is The Void.
我要成为上帝
And I get to play God.
快走
Come on.
你要告诉我怎么用那台装置
Now you're going to show me how to use this fancy gadget of yours.
放心 我叫了些朋友来 保证我们不会被打扰
And don't worry, I've called some friends to make sure we're not disturbed.
抱歉打扰您 有个情况需要您过目
Sorry to bother, madam, but there's something you need to see.
迹象显示10005号地球上 有未经审批的时间开膛手启动
We're getting indications of an unsanctioned Time Ripper activating on Earth-10005.
那是谁负责的区域
Whose district is that?
悖论
Paradox.
【时间开膛手已启动】
感谢你帮忙 亲爱的
Well, thank you so much for your help, darling.
天啊 可算不用扒拉你脑袋了
God. Good to get out of that head.
狗屎一样
What a mess!
招牌上写的莱菲尔德足踝矫正 是致敬死侍的创作者之一罗伯·莱菲尔德 亦是调侃其画脚难看
等等
Stop!
先让群演们走出镜头
Let's give it a beat for the extras to clear.
快走 快走 不会吧
Go, go, go! Oh, my God!
-上帝啊 -见鬼
-Oh. My. God. -Fuck.
BGM：Eric Carmen - 《Make Me Lose Control》
是它
It's her!
过来 宝贝
Come on, girl!
我的小宝贝
That's my girl!
我们再也不会分开了
We don't have to be apart ever, ever again.
永远永远在...
Never, ever...
-抱歉 -操
-Sorry! -Fuck!
美发教父来做什么
What's Cafe Gratitude doing here?
不好意思
Sorry about that.
不怕怕 玛莉·普汀 我来应付
Tremble not, sweet Mary Puppins. I'll handle him.
过来宝贝 爸爸来了
Come here, girl. Papa's here.
不要剥夺这只狗的自由意志
Hey, do not insult this animal's autonomy.
它自己能决定谁当它爸爸
She can decide who her papa is.
你会选谁呢
What's it gonna be, girl, huh?
原装正版演《死侍》的 还是演《留级之王》的
Original recipe or Van Milder here?
Van Milder是瑞安·雷诺兹在《留级之王》中的角色 在大学各种不学无术 花天酒地
真有趣
That's funny.
我也能浅破一下第四堵墙
I can gently tap the fourth wall too.
《假结婚》是瑞安·雷诺兹2009年主演的爱情喜剧 女上司为了自己的签证让男主假扮未婚夫
演《假结婚》的
The Proposal.
你妈 什么意思
The fuck was that?
-你以为我什么人 -你们都闭嘴
-Bitch, you think that's what I do? -Both of you shut up.
闻到什么了
You smell something?
是你
Yeah, you.
很多个你
A lot of you.
死侍头应该是参照了丧尸宇宙中 死侍被砍下的头
跟你说过有一大堆死侍在那
Told you there werea lot of Deadpools over there.
传送门左侧有一对白色翅膀 是漫画26期封面 死侍模仿丘比特的造型
画面最左侧为死侍2099 旁边戴防毒面具的死侍出自漫画《黄金时代死侍》 属于地球-TRN245
大事不妙
That's bad.
传送门中间位置有个带着王冠的死侍 出自漫画《死侍V8》
带有威尔士国旗图案的死侍 由瑞安·雷诺兹名下雷克瑟姆球队的前锋保罗·穆林配音
浪人侍 出自漫画《五浪人》 其他四位是金刚狼 浩克 灵蝶 惩罚者 属于地球-11542
蝉侍 漫画中的邪恶轴心大事件颠倒人物善恶后 内心善良的死侍
画面右侧的死侍服装 与休·杰克曼在电影《马戏之王》中的服装基本相同
看着不是自己人
I take it they're not friendly.
很不幸 说对了
Goodness, no.
抱歉伙计们 游戏结束
Sorry about this, boys. Mission over.
死因 百名杀红眼的死侍
Cause of death, one hundred kill-thirsty Deadpools.
他们是很蠢
They're dumb.
但他们也很能打 除了我
But they can fight. Not me, though.
我也想助你们一臂之力 可惜我骨质疏松...
Would love to get in the mix, but I have low bone density...
而且我得保住我这帅脸
and I have to keep my face safe.
-抱一下 -天啊
-Hold, please. -Oh, God.
听好
All right. Look.
各位
Guys!
旗舰版死侍在此
Deadpool Prime here.
我们不想跟你们开打...
Our fight isn't with you...
想跟我说话
When I want your opinion,
就把金刚狼的屌从嘴里抽出来
I'll take Wolverine's dick out of your mouth.
死侍小子（Kidpool）在漫画中是男孩 属于地球-10330 电影中由瑞安·雷诺兹的二女儿配音
那是青少年死侍 说话最脏的就是她
That's Kidpool. She's the dirtiest.
可以结束了吗
Can we just be done?
女死侍由瑞安·雷诺兹的妻子布蕾克·莱弗利配音
我们才刚开始呢
We're just getting started.
不不不 整个多元宇宙这一套
No, no, no. With the whole multiverse thing.
并不怎么样
It's not great.
它搞得乱七...
It's just been miss...
八糟...
after miss...
乱七八糟
after miss.
《绿野仙踪》先搞了多元宇宙这一套
Look, The Wizard of Ozdid the multiverse first...
他们做得很棒 男同都明白
and they did it best. The gays knew it.
但我们给拍砸了
But we didn't listen.
所以我们接受失败 把这些翻篇
Let's just take the L and move on.
我觉得《终局之战》后面的质量都不错
I think it's been steadily great since Endgame.
你说的什么狗屁玩意儿
What are you talking about?
多元宇宙就要完了
The multiverse is over.
牛仔死侍 属于地球-1108 由马修·麦康纳配音
卡桑德拉会摧毁每条时间线
Cassandy gonna destroy the fuck outta every timeline.
-你们什么也做不了 -还没懂吗
-Y'all can't do shit about it. -Do you not get it?
如果不进地铁阻止她 我们都会死
If we don't go down to the subway and stop her, we all die.
反正老大不想被打扰
Say, the boss lady don't want no disturbances.
想进地铁 先过我们这关
You wanna get down to the subway, you gotta go through us.
乌兹冲锋枪上场
Uzi time, baby.
快闪
Look alive!
-我好像中弹了 -废话
-I think I'm hit. -No shit.
你是故意的
You did that on purpose.
我没有
I did no such thing!
听我说 帅哥
Listen to me, gorgeous.
你的自愈能力需要多久
How long does it take for you to regenerate?
自愈能力？
Regenerate?
你果然是天下第一号白痴
You really are God's perfect idiot, aren't you?
-我没事 -竟然这么说
-I'm okay. -How dare you!
你这冷血的王八蛋
You insensitive son of a bitch!
我怎么知道他不能自愈
How was I supposed to know he doesn't regenerate?
我又不是刮骨的华佗
I'm not a medicine woman.
看 卖甜甜圈的
Look. A donut cart.
-他们就像医院 -什么
-They're practically hospitals. -What?
-也卖急救用品 -并没有
-They sell portable triage units. -They don't.
-我会带你到安全的地方 -他不会
-I'm gonna get you to safety. -He's not.
深呼吸
Deep breath.
嘿 干嘛停下来
Hey, why are we stopping?
我喘口气
I'm just catching my breath.
你的腿没使劲吗 死沉死沉的
What, are your legs on vacation? You're dead weight!
我已经没知觉了
That's because I'm paralyzed.
我们都有问题 听我说
We all have problems. Listen to me.
你会活下去
You're gonna live.
看着我 斯文侍
Look at me, Nicepool.
你会活下去
You're gonna live.
快跟我说
Say it!
我会活下去
I'm gonna live.
跟我一起说 你会活下去
Say it with me. You're gonna live.
我会活下去
I'm gonna live!
大声一点
Say it louder!
我会活下去...
I'm gonna live...
别开枪
Hold your fire!
可爱的小狗狗
Sweet little puppy.
可恶 看来他不行了
God damn it! I don't think he's gonna make it.
他很爱自己的帅脸
God, he loved his face.
我都能尝到他最后这份爱
I can taste his final thought.
他虽然害怕
He was so afraid.
但他英勇牺牲
But he died a hero.
他是被你害死的 蠢货
He died from murder, you dumb fuck.
能缅怀他的只有...
And all I have to remember him by...
这两把镀金点50口径沙漠之鹰手枪
are these two gold-plated,.50 caliber Desert Eagle pistoleros.
这是为了他
This is for him.
准备好了吗
Are you ready?
能干掉一百个你？
I get to kill a hundred yous?
好极了
Fuck yeah, I'm ready.
你别看这种血腥场面
Hey, you don't want to see this, bub.
乖宝贝
That's a good girl.
BGM：Madonna - 《Like A Prayer》
我操
Holy shit.
现在才把这好东西亮出来
You save the good stuff for special occasions?
为了杀戮时刻
Killing mostly.
这两个口爆的把手风阻大吗
What's the wind resistance on those blowjob handles?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我一嫉妒就想酸两句
I'm just a catty bitch when I'm jealous.
好 上吧
All right, let's do this.
火力全开
Maximum effort.
你死了
You're dead.
操他娘啊
Motherfucker.
真盼着我是个聋子
I wish I were deaf.
【友善好邻居：斯坦·李清洁公司】
友善好邻居是蜘蛛侠的形容词 后面始于1922年是指斯坦·李的生日
蜘蛛侠汤姆·赫兰德的弟弟哈里·赫兰德 客串出演了其中一个死侍
我不想死
I don't wanna die. I don't wanna die.
我不想...
I don't wanna...
拜托
Come on.
演砸了
I blew it.
这么多人的长镜头 只给观众留下我这个狗吃屎
After all that, the only thing they're gonna remember is that God awful dismount!
婴儿死侍由瑞安·雷诺兹的小儿子配音
笑什么 小逼崽子
What you laughing at, you little fucker?
看来这些都会自愈
I guess these ones regenerate.
左二是法国死侍 出自漫画《死侍屠杀死侍》
见鬼 没时间跟他们耗
Come on. We don't have time for this.
死侍们
Deadpools!
让开
Stand down.
左边的灰色战衣死侍 造型出自漫画《X特攻队》 彼得与死侍相识也是因此招聘广告
这个死侍跟我一伙的
This Deadpool's with me.
不会吧
Oh, no.
我靠
Holy shit.
那他妈是彼得
That's fucking Peter!
等等 你们都认识彼得？
Wait, you... You guys know Peter?
开玩笑 每个死侍都有一个彼得
You kidding me? Every Deadpool has a Peter.
彼得在每个死侍的世界都是传奇
Shit. Peter's a goddamn legend in every Deadpool's world.
彼得桑
Peter-san.
彼得...
Peter. Peter. Peter.
太棒了 我的彼得
Enjoy my Peter.
现在你们来了 太迟了 都结束了
Oh, now you're here. Oh, well, you're too late. It's all over.
还没有
Not yet, it's not.
不 只差一点点了
No, no, no. We're very close.
最后冲刺 我保证
Homestretch, folks. Promise.
该放手一搏了
Quick, let's up the stakes.
如果她窃取了时间开膛手的能量...
If she steals the Time Ripper's energy...
就能瓦解所有的现实结构...
she has the power to shred the fabric of all realities...
最后只剩虚空存在
until there is nothing left but The Void.
怎么关了它
How do we shut it down?
不知道
I don't know.
现在知道吗
How about now?
这张面具很吓人吧
The mask is really intimidating, huh?
这里指迈克尔·基顿版蝙蝠侠 战衣不能转头 2023年《闪电侠》当中也有调侃
就像蝙蝠侠 但他可以转头
It's like Batman, except he can move his neck.
好 好 听我说
Okay, look, look, look.
时间开膛手由地下的安全屋供能
The Ripper is fed from a secure chamber below ground.
通过汇聚在内部的物质与反物质驱动
It is powered by twin matter and anti-matter feeds converging inside the device.
卡桑德拉·诺瓦正在...
Now, Cassandra Nova...
重新定向开膛手的能量 来终结所有时间线...
is redirecting the Ripper's power to eliminate all timelines...
就从这条开始
starting with this one.
理论上 你们也能阻止她...
Theoretically, you could stop her...
需要让地下安全屋的供能短路
by short-circuiting the feeds in the chamber below.
两条供能线路短接后...
One of you were to create a circuit between the two feeds...
释放出的能量就会摧毁时间开膛手
then the released power would destroy the machine.
-但是 这... -快说
-But, well, but... -Come on, man.
咽不下去 就说出来
If you're not gonna swallow, spit it out.
不管谁接通这股能量 都会死
Whoever formed the bridge would be annihilated.
-我不会死 -我也可以
-I could live with that. -Yeah, I could live with that, too, actually.
我们就像打不死的小强
You know, we survive anything. We're like cockroaches.
这次不一样
Not this time.
这是物质和反物质
This is matter and anti-matter.
它们彼此互为反状态
They do not play nicely with each other.
如果在体内相遇 你会湮灭成原子级
When they mix in your body, you will be atomized.
不信我也得信科学
Trust the laws of physics, if you don't trust me.
就算能撑着把线路短接 但能量释放时...
Even if you lived long enough to make the circuit...
你也会当场送命
you will die down there.
【时间轴完整性】
慢着
Hold off. Hold.
你听到楼上那混蛋说的
You heard that asshole upstairs.
就算成功 我们也是死
Even if we pull this off, we're dead.
彻底死亡
Permanently.
所以得由我去
That's why it's got to be me.
什么
What?
听着...
Look, man...
这本来与你无关
you didn't ask for any of this.
你说得对
You were right.
我骗了你
I lied.
我说那些谎话...
I lied right to your face...
只是为了让你帮我 你已经做的够多了
just to get you to help me. And you did.
你没骗我
You didn't lie.
你是画了个合理的饼
You made an educated wish.
别忘了
Come on.
你还有个世界在等你回去
You got a whole world to go back to.
我一无所有
I got nothing.
一无所有
还是让我来吧
Give me this.
我等了好久才跟你联手
I waited a long time for this team up.
你知道吗
You know something?
你是最棒的金刚狼
You were the best Wolverine.
替我问候你的朋友们
Say hi to your friends for me.
不
No!
开门
Open the door!
你这牺牲太高尚 我都听不见了
I can't hear you over all the noble sacrifice.
你这是为了什么
Why are you fucking doing this?
因为我是...
Because I'm...
漫威救世主
Marvel Jesus.
或者星际迷航里的斯波克
Or Spock.
不好说
Hard to say.
韦德
Wade!
你这个白痴
You fucking idiot!
抱歉 我在拖时间
Sorry, I'm just stalling.
真要牺牲了还是有点慌啊
I think I'm nervous about dying.
本应让我去
This should be me.
替我问候我的朋友们 小狼狗
Say hi to my friends for me, peanut.
韦德
Wade!
你想继续嘴贱 就给我过来
You want to be an annoying prick, do it this side!
你会死在这 你个傻子
You're gonna die in there, you dumb fuck!
【时间轴完整性】
嘿 你不需要这么做
Hey! You don't need to do this.
这么做不是我需要
I'm not doing it 'cause I need it.
而是他们需要我
I'm doing it because they do.
不
No!
他来不及了
He's not gonna make it.
【时间轴完整性】
结束了
It's over.
BGM：Madonna - 《Like A Prayer》
金刚狼
The Wolverine.
他在我的世界曾是英雄
He's a hero in my world.
不管你以为我是谁 你找错人了
Whoever you think I am, you got the wrong guy.
你本来就不是我要找的人
You were always the wrong guy...
直到你直面自己
till you weren't.
韦德
Wade.
韦德 你终于
Wade. You can finally,
终于可以
finally,
有作为了
matter.
凡妮莎
Vanessa.
我想见到凡妮莎
I wanna see Vanessa.
人生第一次
For the first time in my life,
我以穿上这套战衣为荣
I am proud to wear this suit.
它代表我是X战警
It means I'm an X-Man.
我是头号X战警
I am the X-Man.
悖论
Paradox.
你最近很忙啊
You've been busy.
活儿得有人干啊
Well, somebody had to be.
我们读取到这里有异常数据
We had some strange readings from this location.
未经批准启动的时间开膛手不会跟你有关吧
You wouldn't know anything about an unsanctioned Time Ripper, would you?
没有 我完全不知道什么未经核准的时间开膛手
No. No. I wouldn't know anything about an unsanctioned Time Ripper.
也许你该去问卡桑德拉·诺瓦
Maybe you should ask Cassandra Nova.
因为给我打包票...
Because I was assured...
她会一直乖乖关在虚空里 结果却没有...
that she was safely held in The Void. But no...
她刚才就在这 还乱摸我的脑袋
she was here. And she fondled my brain.
怎么会有这种事
How did you let this happen?
你确定自己没参与？
You weren't involved at all?
参与阻止她 我有
In stopping her, yes! Yes. I was.
可是阻止不了
But, not nearly enough.
比不上追她下去的那两人
Not as much as the men who went down there after her.
我的部下
My men.
亦是我的朋友
My friends.
我警告过他们
I warned them.
去了就是送死 但他们还是去了 简直...
That they would be completely obliterated if they went. But they went anyway. Like...
如英雄一般
Like heroes.
因为他们就是英雄
Because that's who they were.
他们做了该做的事
They just did what they had to do.
不顾自身安危
With no concern for their own safety.
现在我们还能站在这里...
The fact that we are all still standing here...
就证明了他们有多英勇
is a testament to their heroism.
但再怎么样 他们也不会回来了
Anyway, there's nothing you or I can do to bring them back now.
他重生了 小宝贝
He has risen, baby girl.
操
Fuck!
BGM：The Goo Goo Dolls - 《Iris》
给你找到新锚定者了
Found your new Anchor Being.
我们好得很 你个人渣
And we're doing just fine, you piece of shit.
确实很好
Fine indeed.
行了
All right.
把你油亮的奶子收起来 发骚的婊
Put your greasy tits away, you preening slut.
我不明白
I don't understand.
为什么你们还活着
How are you two still alive?
没错 一个人去 确实会死
You were right. One of us would have been killed.
但是把死侍与金刚狼放在一起...
But you put a Deadpool and a Wolverine together...
手拉手还放着麦当娜的歌...
make them hold hands while listening to Madonna...
就坚不可摧 你妈逼的
indestructible, motherfucker.
把这个死侍变体送回虚空
Let's get this Deadpool Variant back to The Void.
-等等 什么 -不 其实...
-Wait, hold on. What? -Nope. Actually...
他就是这个宇宙的 跟我一样
This one's homegrown, like me.
他本来就在这里
He belongs here.
你是？
And you are?
彼得侍 可以叫我彼得
Peterpool. But you can call me Peter.
希望你这么叫我
And I hope that you do.
这他妈什么情况
What the fuck is happening here?
你将会受到审判...
You are under judgment...
因启动未经批准的时间开膛手
for operating an unsanctioned Time Ripper.
-带走 -我只是做了你们不敢于做的事
-Take him. -I was just doing what you don't have the guts to do.
放开你的脏手
Get your insolent hands off me!
放开
Get off!
我由衷感谢两位
I'm grateful, gentlemen.
鞠躬就免了
Let's hold the bows.
你把一个欧米茄级的变种人带到了这条时间线
You led an Omega-level mutant to this timeline.
不客气
You're welcome.
-你本不应该出现在这里 -他也不客气
-And you shouldn't even be near this timeline. -He's welcome.
而你 穿这套战衣帅简直太帅了
And you look damn good in that suit.
抱歉帅着你了
I'm so sorry.
我有个不得了的东西给你们看
I wanna show you something. Something huge.
这里指的是漫威CEO凯文·费奇 因其总戴着帽子 确实像童子军教官
童子军团长凯文也常这么说
That's what Scoutmaster Kevin used to say.
看到了吗
Do you see that?
你的宇宙正在恢复
Your universe is regenerating.
不管你在这里做了什么
Whatever you did here...
你不只拯救了你的世界
you not only saved your world.
也让你的时间线免于湮灭
You spared your timeline from extinction.
我该走了
I'd rest up.
看起来你的工作才刚刚开始
I have a feeling your work is only just getting started.
演到90岁
Till you're 90.
等等
Wait!
多亏了有人相助我们才能离开虚空
We couldn't have made it out of The Void without some help...
他们却被世界遗忘了
from some people that the world kind of forgot.
在弃用的删减片段中 暗示牌皇也通过传送门离开了虚空
有没有什么办法能让他们回到自己的世界
Is there any way that you could maybe find a way to bring them home?
我尽我所能
I'll see what I can do.
我跟我朋友保证...
And I promised my friend here...
时变局能逆转他时间线的悲剧
that the TVA could undo some pretty awful shit in his timeline.
可以实现吗
What would you say to that?
改写过去？
Change the past?
他一起拯救了世界
Well, he did help me save the world.
正是这些过往造就了如今的他
And his past made him the man who did it.
顺其自然吧 威尔逊先生
There's nothing to fix, Mr. Wilson.
罗根
Logan.
土耳其烤肉？
Shawarma?
-就它了 -好
-I could eat. -Yeah.
此处指《复联1》片尾第二个彩蛋
复仇者最后也吃的土耳其烤肉
You know, the Avengers discovered shawarma.
有你加入是他们的福气
They'd be lucky to have you.
不会吧
Oh, come on.
太赞了
Fuck off!
过来 我的小可爱
Come here, my little cunchkin.
你才是最后的赢家
Yes, it's you. You're a survivor.
这个世界太完美了
Oh, all is right in the world.
真的
Yes, it is.
今后有什么方向吗
So what are you gonna do next?
我会找到方向的 向来如此
I'll figure it out. I always do.
好吧
All right.
该说再见了？
So I'll probably see you around?
BGM：Aretha Franklin - 《You're All I Need To Get By》 (with The Royal Philharmonic Orchestra)
也许不见了
Probably not.
再见 老兄
See you, bub.
罗根
Logan.
艾尔 我回来了
Al. I'm back.
都几点了
About damn time.
带着货吗
You holding?
没有魔鬼的头皮屑（可卡因的俚语）了...
I'm all outta devil's dandruff...
-哆嗦得跟最大档跳蛋一样 -谢了 艾尔
-and I'm shaking like an angry vibrator. -Thank you, Al.
有客人
We have company.
艾瑟雅 这是...
Althea, this is...
这是罗根
This is Logan.
很高兴见到你 罗根
Nice to meet you, Logan.
我也是
Nice to meet you, too.
这只菊花上的包浆屎嘎渣是玛莉·普汀
And this little ancient anal shit-knot is Mary Puppins.
我喜欢叫它狗侍
Or as I like to call her, Dogpool.
要不要来一下
You want to treat yourself to a little stroke?
-那是舌头 -我操 啥鸡巴玩意
-Get the tongue. There it is. -Oh, my God! Motherfucker!
就像犰狳猛强暴了一只地精...
Right? It's like an armadillo fucked a gremlin, angrily...
在满是淋病的床上...
in a bed of gonorrhea...
一日一天才罢休
and didn't stop till the sun came up.
人人都想有作为
Everyone wants to matter.
却发现不必当漫威救世主也做得到
Turns out that you don't need to be Marvel Jesus to do it.
只要睁开眼睛 环顾四周
You just need to open your eyes and look around.
幸运的话...
And if you're lucky...
你会找到几个朋友
you'll find a few friends.
几个老朋友...
Old friends...
还有一些新朋友
and some new ones too.
把狗给我 主动一点
Give me the fucking dog. Talk to the girl.
最近很忙啊
You've been busy.
我是为了你
I did it for you.
就算你不在乎 我还是为了你
And even if you don't want me, I did it for you.
结果...
It turns out...
我就是拯救世界的料
I am the world-saving type.
披萨盒子上写的Feige's Famous 同样是指凯文·费奇 电影第一部也曾出现
看看这一桌 就是证据
Just look around this table if you want proof.
最棒的是什么呢
And the best part?
有时我们拯救的人...
Sometimes the people we save...
同样会拯救我们
well, they save us right back.
【请勿离开 2:00:17精彩继续】
你不是唯一有天赋的人
You're not the only one with gifts.
这是什么地方
What is this place?
《X战警》
BGM：Green Day - 《Good Riddance》 (Time Of Your Life)
【艾丽卡】
战衣不错
Nice suit.
闭嘴 斯坦·李
Zip it, Stan Lee.
我喜欢死侍的漫画风格
I really like the, the art in the Deadpool comics.
【瑞安·雷诺兹】
我总觉得自己有点像他
You know, I just always felt a kind of a kinship to him.
我想总有一天我会演这个角色
And I just thought, I'd like to play that guy someday.
我等了三周才拍一个镜头
I was there for three weeks before I shot a single thing.
【休·杰克曼】
在拍摄的第一天...
At our first day of shooting...
我特别紧张
I was so nervous, man.
大家都在问 这家伙是谁
Everyone was sort of going, "Who's this guy?"
很常出现那种质疑...
You know, there was a lot of that and...
他行不行啊
you know, "Is he gonna deliver or not?"
你能感受到那种种压力
You can feel all that kind of pressure.
绝对是服装的问题
It's always the suit's fault.
不是演员
Never the actor.
【罗根】
-这是... -唯一的办法
-This is... -The only way.
原来死亡是这种感觉
So this is what it feels like.
现在灯光亮起
And there's the lights.
为了医学研究
For medical research.
-再见 拍完了 -再见
-Bye-bye, video. -Bye.
【二十世纪福克斯】
【等等 2:06:41后面还有彩蛋】
我受够了那些卑劣的谣言 说我害死了强尼
I'm tired of these absolutely vile rumors that I got Johnny killed.
看看录像
Let's look at the tape.
在虚空中
In The Void...
你不是艾利奥斯的大餐
you're either food for Alioth...
就是她的奴隶
or you work for her.
继续 强尼
Go on, Johnny.
跟你们说她是谁
And I'll tell you who "her" is.
卡桑德拉·诺瓦
Cassandra Nova.
妄自尊大的傻逼神经病
A megalomaniacal, psychotic asshole.
行尸走肉一般的嗜血妖女 青石板胸豆奶稀
A finger licking dead-inside pixie slab of third rate dime-store nut-milk.
-跟你说她该干什么 -洗耳恭听
-And I'll tell you what she can do. -I'm listening.
她只适合舔我翘臀里面的原味菊花 再一路滚回她那秃顶的地狱
She can lick my goddamn cinnamon ring clean and kick rocks all the way to bald hell.
其实也不怕她扒我一层皮...
In fact, I don't give a shit if she removes all my skin and...
跟挤爆的万圣节人皮气球一样
pops me like some nightmarish blood balloon.
就算最后我这插飞机杯的假屌...
If the last thing I do in this godforsaken cum-gutter existence...
能把那贱婊子操到冒火星 我也不会含笑而终
is light that fuck-box on fire, I still won't die happy.
-我操 这片酬值了 -没错 韦德
-Holy shit, girl. You crazy. -That's right, Wade.
想让老子含笑而终 除非...
I won't be happy until...
一泡尿浇灭她冒火星的焦尸 再把它中出成爆浆鸡排...
I've urinated on her freshly barbecued corpse and husk-fucked the charred remains...
一边把红坦克舔成红蛋克
while gargling Juggernaut's juggernuts.
你可以照搬我原话
And you can quote me.
好
OKay.
逮到你奶奶个嘴了
Got you, fuckface.
漫威影业